<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jobs>
   <job>
      <company>UOFMARYLANDMEDSYS</company>
      <jobdescription_opt><![CDATA[<p><strong>Care Manager</br> </strong><em>(Full-Time)</br> Towson, MD</em></p>
<p>We are looking for talented professionals to join our team at University of Maryland St. Joseph Medical Center.&#xa0;&#xa0;</p>
<p>When you come to University of Maryland St. Joseph Medical Center, you’re coming to more than simply a beautiful 37-acre, 224- bed suburban Towson, MD campus. You’re embarking on a professional journey that encourages opportunities, values a team atmosphere, and makes convenience and flexibility a priority.</p>
<p><strong>As a team member at St. Joseph Medical Center, you’ll experience:</strong></p>
<ul>
 <li><strong>A</strong> <strong>supportive and collaborative</strong> work environment.</li>
 <li><strong>A comprehensive benefits package</strong> including health, vision and dental coverage including prescription drug coverage – Tax-Free Savings Plans, Tuition Reimbursement, and generous paid time off.</li>
 <li><strong>Free</strong> Parking &amp; On-Site Fitness Center</li>
 <li><strong>Recognition:</strong> We have a positive points recognition program designed to reward and recognize our outstanding employees; employees can also recognize their peers</li>
 <li>On-Site Daycare</li>
</ul>
<p></br><strong>Job Summary</strong></br>The Care Manager coordinates the care and service of selected patient populations across the continuum.&#xa0;He/ she works collaboratively with physicians and other members of the health care team to achieve the&#xa0;highest quality clinical outcomes with the most cost effective use of available resources. The Care Manager&#xa0;assumes responsibility for an interdisciplinary process which assesses, plans, implements, monitors and</br>measures the effectiveness of interventions to meet patients’ treatment and transitional needs.</p>
<p><strong>Education</strong></br>* 2 year / Associate's Degree (Required)</br>* High School Diploma or GED (Required)</br>4 year / Bachelor's Degree (Preferred)</br></br></br><strong>Certification / Licensure / Registration</strong></br>*State Registered Nurse License (Required)</br>CCM Case Management Certification (Preferred)</br></br></br><strong>Experience and Skills</strong></br>*2 - 4 years Familiarity with health care reimbursement systems (Required)</br>*4 - 6 years Acute care hospital or similar venue. (Required)</br>2 - 4 years Case management, discharge planning or utilization management (Preferred)</br>Required Skills: Strong Verbal Communications Skills, Strong Written Communications Skills, Excellent</br>Interpersonal Skills, Medical Terminology</p>]]></jobdescription_opt>
      <jobid>11131_138742</jobid>
      <jobtitle>Care Manager</jobtitle>
      <jobtype>FULL_TIME</jobtype>
      <location>Towson,MD,United States</location>
      <logo>https://dev-jbk-ai.s3.amazonaws.com/company-logos/d-uploads/1619183043611-UOFMARYLANDMEDSYS.png</logo>
      <occupationalcategory>11-9111.00,Medical and Health Services Managers</occupationalcategory>
      <postalCode>21286</postalCode>
      <salary null="true" />
      <salaryEstimate null="true" />
      <sameas>https://www.umms.org/</sameas>
      <url>https://click.appcast.io/track/927krkk?cs=jsq&amp;exch=16&amp;jg=3g0s&amp;bid=09M1E99kMPPzVZLoZLnQOQ==</url>
   </job>
   <job>
      <company>UOFMARYLANDMEDSYS</company>
      <jobdescription_opt><![CDATA[<p><strong>Registered Nurse (RN) – Emergency Department </strong></br>U of M Baltimore Washington Medical Center</br>Full-Time – Evening.</br>Glen Burnie, Maryland</p>
<p><strong>The Power of Caring</strong><strong></br></strong>Within all of us there is untold power. An unstoppable strength. A desire to do more.</p>
<p><em>Join our talented team of Registered Nurses and experience the highest level of appreciation at UM Baltimore Washington Medical Center</em> — <em>named <strong>Top Workplace</strong> in the Baltimore area by The Baltimore Sun two years in a row (2019 &amp; 2020); </em>Top Workplace in the USA<em> for 2021!</em></p>
<p><em>At University of Maryland Baltimore Washington Medical Center, our registered nurses have earned the highest level of respect as a critical factor in our success— and that of our patients. As part of the acclaimed University of Maryland Medical System, our facility is one of three </em><strong>ANCC Pathway to Excellence®</strong><em> designated hospitals in Maryland. UM BWMC features one of the state’s busiest emergency departments, as well as a team of experts who care for our community and one another. </em></p>
<p><em>Click </em>HERE<em> to meet our Chief Nursing Officer and learn more about nursing at UM BWMC.</em></p>
<p><strong>Responsibilities/Tasks</strong></p>
<p>This role is considered the minimum role for&#xa0;all nurses at BWMC who have greater than (&gt;) 12 months experience.</p>
<ul>
 <li>This&#xa0;nurse will be competent in the skills/knowledge required and fully&#xa0;participate in unit governance.</li>
 <li>Independently provides and coordinates care provided to patients within a clinical specialty.</li>
 <li>Serves as a&#xa0;fully effective and participative member of the multidisciplinary patient care services team.&#xa0;</li>
 <li>Demonstrates and models the full range of nursing&#xa0;professional practice in both care provided and in participation in development of strategies to improve patient outcomes, satisfaction with&#xa0;service and cost effectiveness at the unit level.&#xa0;</li>
 <li>Strives to provide an&#xa0;environment where patients, families, and colleagues collaborate in the&#xa0;delivery of care.</li>
 <li>Is accountable to peers for the advancement of group practice on the unit, and to the nurse manager for the totality of work performance.</li>
 <li>Is accountable to hold the Service Standards of the Nursing&#xa0;Mission, Vision and Values</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>As a Registered Nurse at UM BWMC, you’ll experience:</strong></p>
<ul>
 <li>An organization that supports, recognizes and invests in their nurses.</li>
 <li>Our <strong>Professional Advancement Model (PAM)</strong> designed to recognize and reward nurses based on their professional contributions to advancing the practice and profession of nursing.&#xa0;</li>
 <li>An <strong>environment of excellence</strong> focused on quality and inter-professional <strong>collaboration</strong>.</li>
 <li>A <strong>comprehensive benefits</strong> package including health, vision and dental coverage including prescription drug coverage – Tax-Free Savings Plans, Tuition Reimbursement and more!</li>
 <li><strong>Work Life Balance: </strong>You’ll accrue annual leave; we offer dependent care reimbursement, short/long term disability and an employee assistance program.</li>
 <li><strong>Educational Assistance:</strong>We support your continuing education and career advancement by offering tuition reimbursement &amp; continuing education options.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
 <li>American Heart Association (AHA) BLS required upon hire</li>
 <li>Must meet all unit specific certification requirements: (PALS, ACLS, NRP)</li>
 <li>Ability to learn and use computer systems in order to manage patient information</li>
 <li>Demonstrated effective interpersonal, verbal and written communications skills</li>
 <li>Meets licensing&#xa0;requirements to practice as a registered nursing in the State of&#xa0;Maryland</li>
 <li>1+ year of Emergency Dept experience (preferred)</li>
</ul>]]></jobdescription_opt>
      <jobid>11131_131080</jobid>
      <jobtitle>Registered Nurse (RN) - Emergency Department</jobtitle>
      <jobtype>FULL_TIME</jobtype>
      <location>Glen Burnie,MD,United States</location>
      <logo>https://dev-jbk-ai.s3.amazonaws.com/company-logos/d-uploads/1619183043611-UOFMARYLANDMEDSYS.png</logo>
      <occupationalcategory>29-1141.00,Registered Nurses</occupationalcategory>
      <postalCode>21061</postalCode>
      <salary null="true" />
      <salaryEstimate null="true" />
      <sameas>https://www.umms.org/</sameas>
      <url>https://click.appcast.io/track/7tvtory?cs=jsq&amp;exch=16&amp;jg=3g0s&amp;bid=09M1E99kMPPzVZLoZLnQOQ==</url>
   </job>
   <job>
      <company>UOFMARYLANDMEDSYS</company>
      <jobdescription_opt><![CDATA[<table>
 <tbody>
  <tr>
   <td>
    <table>
     <tbody>
      <tr>
       <td><p><strong>Transitional Nurse Navigator - Care Management, Harmony</strong></br> <strong>Full Time - Days</strong></br> <strong>Baltimore, MD</br> </br> </strong></p><p>The Transitional Nurse Navigator (TNN) is responsible for seeking and implementing interventions, methodologies, and best practices for the high risk population. Using an evidence-based tool, the TNN identifies and assesses the patient for priority needs, key areas for&#xa0; needed support and services that contribute to readmissions; develop care plans and when appropriate refers for services to assist in navigating barriers to care.&#xa0;&#xa0;<strong>(About the Facility)</strong></p><p><strong>We're making Maryland stronger!</strong></p><p>With roots that go as far back as 1895, the UM Rehabilitation &amp; Orthopaedic Institute continues to be a&#xa0;<strong>pioneer in orthopaedics and neurological disorders</strong>. From bones to brains, our cutting-edge center heals even the most serious of injuries, specializing in everything from total joint replacement to&#xa0;<strong>spinal cord injuries</strong>&#xa0;and&#xa0;<strong>neurological conditions</strong>. Our surgeries take place in 6 operating rooms designed for Orthopaedic Surgery combined with our efficient 7-bed Medical Surgical Unit. And our rehabilitation occurs in our innovative William Donald Schaefer Rehabilitation Center. In total, our 141-bed facility welcomes over 3,000 patients every year. As the state’s&#xa0;<strong>largest provider of inpatient rehabilitation services</strong>, we offer some of the most advanced therapies for&#xa0;<strong>stroke, spinal cord injury, traumatic brain injury, orthopaedic and sports injury, among many others.</strong></p><p><strong>Job Summary</strong>:&#xa0;</p>
        <ul>
         <li>Consistently expresses and demonstrates respect, compassion and courtesy for patients, family/visitors, and team members.&#xa0;</li>
         <li>Assists the clinical nurse in providing individualized patient care consistent with the mission and values of University of Maryland Rehabilitation &amp; Orthopaedic Institute and in accordance within the scope of practice, professional, and regulatory standards.&#xa0;</li>
         <li>Assists the clinical nurse in providing care appropriate to the age, culture, ethnicity, spirituality, and individual diagnostic needs of the persons served.&#xa0;</li>
         <li>Accountable to the clinical nurse, patients and families for processes and outcomes during an episode of care.&#xa0;</li>
         <li>Serves as a fully engaged member of the interdisciplinary patient care services team.&#xa0;</li>
         <li>Participates in cost effective strategies that optimize patient outcomes.</li>
        </ul><p><strong></br> </br> </strong></p></td>
      </tr>
     </tbody>
    </table><p><strong></br> </br> </strong></p></td>
  </tr>
 </tbody>
</table>
<ul>
 <li>Bachelor’s degree in nursing or related field required.</li>
 <li>Current Maryland State Licensure as a Registered Nurse.</li>
 <li>Three (3) years of experience in care transitions/care coordination.</li>
 <li>Current CRP certification.</li>
</ul>]]></jobdescription_opt>
      <jobid>11131_138769</jobid>
      <jobtitle>Transitional Nurse Navigator (RN) - Care Management, Harmony</jobtitle>
      <jobtype>FULL_TIME</jobtype>
      <location>Baltimore,MD,United States</location>
      <logo>https://dev-jbk-ai.s3.amazonaws.com/company-logos/d-uploads/1619183043611-UOFMARYLANDMEDSYS.png</logo>
      <occupationalcategory>53-3022.00,Bus Drivers, School or Special Client</occupationalcategory>
      <postalCode>21202</postalCode>
      <salary null="true" />
      <salaryEstimate null="true" />
      <sameas>https://www.umms.org/</sameas>
      <url>https://click.appcast.io/track/927krkx?cs=jsq&amp;exch=16&amp;jg=3g0s&amp;bid=0vfOigRjL4ICTE-1fXrDXw==</url>
   </job>
   <job>
      <company>UOFMARYLANDMEDSYS</company>
      <jobdescription_opt><![CDATA[<span>Registered Nurse - NICU</span></br> 
<span>Full-time-Night Shift</span></br> 
<span>Towson, Maryland</span></br> </br>
<p>When you come to University of Maryland St. Joseph Medical Center, you’re coming to more than simply a beautiful 37-acre, 224- bed suburban Towson, MD campus. You’re embarking on a professional journey that encourages opportunities, values a team atmosphere, and makes convenience and flexibility a priority.</br> </br> </br> </br> <span><strong>About the Unit</strong></span></p>
<p>St. Joseph Medical Center’s neonatal intensive care unit is a 20-bed Level III NICU. The state-of-the-art unit has an innovative pinwheel design that allows optimal patient care while maximizing family privacy.</p>
<p>The NICU nursing team provides care to premature and full-term infants born at St. Joseph Medical Center that might experience a wide variety of problems or conditions.</br> </br> </p>
<p><strong>As a Registered Nurse at UM St. Joseph, you’ll experience:</strong></p>
<ul>
 <li>A&#xa0;<strong>supportive and collaborative</strong>&#xa0;work environment</li>
 <li><strong>A comprehensive benefits package</strong>&#xa0;including health, vision and dental coverage including prescription drug coverage – Tax-Free Savings Plans, Tuition Reimbursement and more!</li>
 <li><strong>Free</strong>&#xa0;<strong>Parking</strong>&#xa0;&amp; On-Site Fitness Center</li>
 <li><strong>Recognition:</strong>&#xa0;We have a positive points recognition program designed to reward and recognize our outstanding employees; employees can also recognize their peers</li>
 <li>On-Site Daycare</li>
</ul>
<p></br> </p>
<ul>
 <li>Graduation from an accredited nursing education program approved by the Board of Nursing.&#xa0; BSN preferred.</li>
 <li>Currently licensed as an RN in the state of Maryland.</li>
 <li>BLS certification&#xa0;</li>
 <li><strong>Minimum of two years of experience in a Level III NICU required.</strong></li>
</ul></br></br>
<strong>&#xa0; &#xa0; &#xa0; &#xa0; &#xa0; &#xa0; &#xa0; &#xa0; &#xa0; &#xa0; &#xa0; &#xa0; &#xa0; &#xa0; &#xa0; &#xa0; &#xa0; &#xa0; SIGN ON BONUS - $3K FOR TWO YEARS OR MORE EXPERENCE REQUIRED</strong>]]></jobdescription_opt>
      <jobid>11131_136634</jobid>
      <jobtitle>Registered Nurse (RN) - NICU</jobtitle>
      <jobtype>FULL_TIME</jobtype>
      <location>Towson,MD,United States</location>
      <logo>https://dev-jbk-ai.s3.amazonaws.com/company-logos/d-uploads/1619183043611-UOFMARYLANDMEDSYS.png</logo>
      <occupationalcategory>29-1141.00,Registered Nurses</occupationalcategory>
      <postalCode>21286</postalCode>
      <salary null="true" />
      <salaryEstimate null="true" />
      <sameas>https://www.umms.org/</sameas>
      <url>https://click.appcast.io/track/8c4r802?cs=jsq&amp;exch=16&amp;jg=3g0s&amp;bid=09M1E99kMPPzVZLoZLnQOQ==</url>
   </job>
   <job>
      <company>UOFMARYLANDMEDSYS</company>
      <jobdescription_opt><![CDATA[<table>
 <tbody>
  <tr>
   <td colspan="4">
    <table>
     <tbody>
      <tr>
       <td colspan="4">
        <table>
         <tbody>
          <tr>
           <td colspan="4">
            <table>
             <tbody>
              <tr>
               <td colspan="4"><p><strong>Registered Nurse (RN) – Med Surg GI/Oncology/Dialysis</br> </strong><span>Part-Time – Night Shift</br> </span><span>Towson, Maryland</br> </span></p><p>We are seeking a Registered Nurse to join our nursing team at University of Maryland St. Joseph Medical Center.&#xa0;&#xa0;</p><p>When you come to University of Maryland St. Joseph Medical Center, you’re coming to more than simply a beautiful 37-acre, 224- bed suburban Towson, MD campus. You’re embarking on a professional journey that encourages opportunities, values a team atmosphere, and makes convenience and flexibility a priority.</p><p><strong>As a Registered Nurse at UM St. Joseph, you’ll experience:</strong></p>
                <ul>
                 <li>A&#xa0;<strong>supportive and collaborative</strong>&#xa0;work environment</li>
                 <li><strong>A comprehensive benefits package</strong>&#xa0;including health, vision and dental coverage including prescription drug coverage – Tax-Free Savings Plans, Tuition Reimbursement and more!</li>
                 <li><strong>Free</strong>&#xa0;<strong>Parking</strong>&#xa0;&amp; On-Site Fitness Center</li>
                 <li><strong>Recognition:</strong>&#xa0;We have a positive points recognition program designed to reward and recognize our outstanding employees; employees can also recognize their peers</li>
                 <li>On-Site Daycare</li>
                </ul><p><strong>Unit Details:</strong>&#xa0;7 East/West is a 24-bed inpatient medical-surgical unit which also specializes in the care of the oncology, GU, and GI patient. Nurses, physicians, and social workers collaborate with support services to provide an interdisciplinary approach to meet the care needs of the patient population across the continuum. The staff members provide care to adult (age 18 and older) oncology, medical, surgical, wound care, gastroenterology, and urology patients. Chemotherapy administration is an important component of our oncology unit and is given by chemotherapy certified registered nurses.</br> </br> <strong>Job Summary:</br> </strong>The Registered Nurse is responsible for patient care in collaboration with interdisciplinary health care providers to assess, plan, intervene, evaluate and document care in an individualized and age appropriate manner which promotes patient safety and healing and according to hospital policy.</p></td>
              </tr>
             </tbody>
            </table></td>
          </tr>
         </tbody>
        </table></td>
      </tr>
     </tbody>
    </table></td>
  </tr>
 </tbody>
</table>
<strong>Education</strong></br> 2 year / Associate's Degree: Nursing&#xa0;</br> 4 year / Bachelor's Degree: BS in Nursing and/or active pursuit of advanced degree or specialty certification.</br> (Preferred)</br> </br> 
<strong>Certification / Licensure / Registration</strong></br> BLS Certification (Required)</br> State Registered Nurse License (Required)</br> </br> 
<strong>Required Skills</br> </strong>Strong Verbal Communications Skills, Strong Written Communications Skills, Excellent&#xa0;Interpersonal Skills, General Clerical Skills, Basic Computer Skills, Excellent Organizational Skills, Strong&#xa0;Customer Services Skills, Proven Analytical Skills]]></jobdescription_opt>
      <jobid>11131_137523</jobid>
      <jobtitle>Registered Nurse (RN) Med Surg</jobtitle>
      <jobtype>PART_TIME</jobtype>
      <location>Towson,MD,United States</location>
      <logo>https://dev-jbk-ai.s3.amazonaws.com/company-logos/d-uploads/1619183043611-UOFMARYLANDMEDSYS.png</logo>
      <occupationalcategory>29-1141.00,Registered Nurses</occupationalcategory>
      <postalCode>21286</postalCode>
      <salary null="true" />
      <salaryEstimate null="true" />
      <sameas>https://www.umms.org/</sameas>
      <url>https://click.appcast.io/track/8lk73ly?cs=jsq&amp;exch=16&amp;jg=3g0s&amp;bid=09M1E99kMPPzVZLoZLnQOQ==</url>
   </job>
   <job>
      <company>UOFMARYLANDMEDSYS</company>
      <jobdescription_opt><![CDATA[<p><strong>Registered Nurse (RN) – Emergency Department</strong></br> UM Capital Region Health&#xa0;</br> Cheverly, MD</p>
<p><strong>$20,000 Sign-On Bonus&#xa0;</strong>available for new-hire RNs with a minimum of two years Emergency Department experience.</p>
<p>&#xa0;As the second busiest Trauma Centers in Maryland, we will transform to a five-bay Trauma Resuscitation Unit staffed with a multidisciplinary team ready to admit, resuscitate, stabilize and treat those whose lives are threatened by time-sensitive injuries.</p>
<p>The nursing staff maintains the highest level of critical care and resuscitation knowledge and skills and work collaboratively with a unified approach toward the care of the injured patient.</p>
<p>The Trauma Center at UMCAP is seeking experienced Registered Nurses with a desire to join our premier multidisciplinary team in our Trauma Resuscitation Unit.</p>
<p>UM Capital Region Health is recruiting experienced Emergency Department RNs to join our award-winning team.&#xa0;&#xa0;</p>
<p>Are you ready to get back to your calling of patient care? To be respected by your peers and have your voice heard by your physicians? To regain your work-life balance and have time and resources to further your education? To be part of a cohesive team that gets to work on every cardiac case and be there with your patients from admission to discharge?&#xa0;&#xa0;</p>
<p>If you are ready to get back to the core mission of nursing and patient care, UM Capital Region Health wants to talk to you!</p>
<p>UM Capital Region Health is about to&#xa0;changeUP&#xa0;everything with the construction of UM Capital Region Medical Center, a new, state-of-the-art hospital facility in Largo, MD. On track to open in April of 2021, our new Medical Center will feature a dedicated Emergency Department which will be a center of excellence in heart care in Prince George’s County.</p>
<p><strong>What we offer:</strong></p>
<ul>
 <li>Opportunity to work with a small, cohesive team of experienced professionals.</li>
 <li><strong>A comprehensive benefits package</strong>&#xa0;including health, vision and dental coverage including prescription drug coverage.</li>
 <li><strong>Great Work Life Balance:&#xa0;</strong>You’ll accrue paid annual leave; we offer dependent care reimbursement, short/long term disability and an employee assistant program.</li>
 <li><strong>Competitive salary</strong></li>
 <li><strong>Educational Assistance:</strong>&#xa0;We support your continuing education and career advancement by offering tuition reimbursement.</li>
</ul>Meet our Chief Nursing Officer, Dr. Vanzetta V. James and learn more about nursing at UM Capital Region Health
<ul>
 <li>Graduation from an accredited nursing education program approved by the Board of Nursing.&#xa0; BSN preferred.</li>
 <li>Currently licensed as an RN in the state of Maryland.</li>
 <li>BLS certification.</li>
 <li>1-2 years of Emergency Room experience.&#xa0;&#xa0;</li>
</ul>]]></jobdescription_opt>
      <jobid>11131_140443</jobid>
      <jobtitle>Clinical Nurse ll Emergency Department</jobtitle>
      <jobtype>FULL_TIME</jobtype>
      <location>Cheverly,MD,United States</location>
      <logo>https://dev-jbk-ai.s3.amazonaws.com/company-logos/d-uploads/1619183043611-UOFMARYLANDMEDSYS.png</logo>
      <occupationalcategory>29-1141.04,Clinical Nurse Specialists</occupationalcategory>
      <postalCode>20785</postalCode>
      <salary null="true" />
      <salaryEstimate null="true" />
      <sameas>https://www.umms.org/</sameas>
      <url>https://click.appcast.io/track/9nm9vsk?cs=jsq&amp;exch=16&amp;jg=3g0s&amp;bid=viVMAPGFWwJQTmWThIkjXQ==</url>
   </job>
   <job>
      <company>UOFMARYLANDMEDSYS</company>
      <jobdescription_opt><![CDATA[<p><strong>Registered Nurse (RN) – Cardiac Operating Room</br> </strong><em>Full-Time -&#xa0; Rotating (M-F 0630-1900 S-S Call)</br> Baltimore, Maryland</em></p>
<p>Come elevate your skills and experience by working with a world-class 800-bed,&#xa0;<strong>Magnet-designated Academic Medical Center</strong>&#xa0;with comprehensive and technologically advanced surgical suites.&#xa0;</p>
<p>We are looking for a Registered Nurse (RN) for<strong>&#xa0;Cardiac Operating Room&#xa0;</strong>to join our nursing team at the University Of Maryland Medical Center (UMMC). &#xa0;</p>
<p>UMMC has five operating rooms dedicated to Cardiac Surgery.&#xa0; The Cardiac OR is a regional referral center for the most difficult cardiac cases.&#xa0; Using the most advanced treatment options and therapies, cardiac surgical services range from repairing&#xa0;congenital&#xa0;heart defects in infants and children to performing&#xa0;heart transplantation and other complex procedures&#xa0;for high-risk adult patients.&#xa0;&#xa0;</p>
<p><strong>As a Registered Nurse at UMMC, you’ll experience:</strong></p>
<ul>
 <li>A&#xa0;<strong>supportive and collaborative</strong>&#xa0;work environment</li>
 <li>An&#xa0;<strong>Achievable Professional Advancement Model:&#xa0;</strong>Opportunities to progress in function, skills, and pay through our achievable promotion schedule;</li>
 <li>&#xa0;The opportunity to work in a specialized care environment at an&#xa0;<strong>Academic Medical Center&#xa0;</strong>with nursing centered care model and&#xa0;<strong>Magnet Designation;</strong></li>
 <li><strong>A comprehensive benefits package</strong>&#xa0;including health, vision, and dental coverage including prescription drug coverage, Tax-Free Savings Plans, and more!</li>
 <li>A&#xa0;<strong>highly competitive wage scale</strong>: Annual merit increases and a base wage scale that is measured against market standards.</li>
 <li><strong>Generous tuition reimbursement</strong>&#xa0;of up to $10,000 per year for your graduate degree at the University of Maryland School of Nursing.</li>
</ul>
<p>Located in downtown Baltimore near the Inner Harbor and Camden Yards, you won’t find a more vibrant place to work!&#xa0;&#xa0;</p>
<ul>
 <li>Currently licensed as an RN in the state of Maryland or eligible to practice under a compact license;</li>
 <li><strong>Must have one-year nursing experience&#xa0;in Cardiac OR&#xa0;with solid knowledge and clinical skills required;</strong></li>
 <li>BSN preferred (Associates Nurses with 1+ years of experience in an inpatient facility, outpatient surgical office, or other environment performing surgical services&#xa0;to patients;</li>
 <li><strong>All qualified Nurses MUST have relevant clinical work experience related to Cardiac OR</strong></li>
</ul>]]></jobdescription_opt>
      <jobid>11131_133974</jobid>
      <jobtitle>Registered Nurse (RN) - Cardiac OR</jobtitle>
      <jobtype>FULL_TIME</jobtype>
      <location>Baltimore,MD,United States</location>
      <logo>https://dev-jbk-ai.s3.amazonaws.com/company-logos/d-uploads/1619183043611-UOFMARYLANDMEDSYS.png</logo>
      <occupationalcategory>29-1141.00,Registered Nurses</occupationalcategory>
      <postalCode>21202</postalCode>
      <salary null="true" />
      <salaryEstimate null="true" />
      <sameas>https://www.umms.org/</sameas>
      <url>https://click.appcast.io/track/7tvtolh?cs=jsq&amp;exch=16&amp;jg=3g0s&amp;bid=09M1E99kMPPzVZLoZLnQOQ==</url>
   </job>
   <job>
      <company>Boyne Resorts</company>
      <jobdescription_opt><![CDATA[<b>Overview</b></br></br>As a 
<strong>Line Cook </strong>you are responsible for preparing food, helping the kitchen staff in preparation of food items, setting up assigned station in compliance with standards set by Chef. As a Boyne Mountain team member, there are so many awesome perks for you to take advantage of, such as: ski passes, golf passes, waterpark passes, and discounts for food, beverages, retail, daycare, and so much more! To learn more about Boyne Mountain Resort, employment perks, and employee testimonials, click here - Boyne Mountain Employment !</br></br>"Work Where You Love To Play!" at Boyne Mountain Resort.</br></br>
<b>Responsibilities</b></br></br>The 
<strong>Line Cook's </strong>typical job functions include: </br>
<ul>
 <li> Preparing food according to food handling guidelines and cooking procedures</li>
 <li> Measuring and mixing ingredients according to recipe or use record to prepare and prep food items</li>
 <li> Stocking and maintaining sufficient levels of food products at line stations to assure a smooth service period</li>
 <li> Communicating and coordinating production with other cooks, wait staff and members of the food and beverage team</li>
 <li> Possessing knowledge and/or become familiar with all kitchen equipment</li>
 <li> Adjusting thermostat controls to regulate temperature of ovens, broilers, grills, roasters, kettles, etc</li>
 <li> Observing and testing foods being cooked by tasting, smelling, and piercing with thermometer to determine proper preparation and cooking</li>
 <li> Plating and portioning food and maintain consistency according to presentation specifications, using records or specs</li>
 <li> Labeling, dating and rotating all stored food</li>
 <li> Performing closing procedures including equipment maintenance and shut off, cleaning, sanitation, and organization of kitchen, walk-in coolers, and all storage areas</li>
</ul></br></br>
<b>Qualifications</b></br></br>This position may for you if: </br>
<ul>
 <li> You are 18 years old </li>
 <li> You have achieved a high school diploma or general education degree (GED) </li>
 <li> You have previous kitchen experience </li>
 <li> You are available to work days, evenings, weekends and holidays </li>
</ul>]]></jobdescription_opt>
      <jobid>13819_9519-0e9197c0ab3fbc33ea24f63806887f31</jobid>
      <jobtitle>Line Cook | Everett's</jobtitle>
      <jobtype>FULL_TIME</jobtype>
      <location>Vanderbilt,MI,United States</location>
      <logo>https://dev-jbk-ai.s3.amazonaws.com/company-logos/d-uploads/1621582705622-Boyne_Resorts_Logo.png</logo>
      <occupationalcategory>35-2014.00,Cooks, Restaurant</occupationalcategory>
      <postalCode>49795</postalCode>
      <salary null="true" />
      <salaryEstimate null="true" />
      <sameas>https://boyneresorts.com/</sameas>
      <url>https://click.appcast.io/track/9gg4v5m?cs=jsq&amp;exch=1a&amp;jg=3t1b&amp;bid=SSAKDDdbKVFCOLsOsUlBHA==</url>
   </job>
   <job>
      <company>Boyne Resorts</company>
      <jobdescription_opt><![CDATA[<b>Overview</b></br></br>As a 
<strong>Line Cook </strong>you are responsible for preparing food, helping the kitchen staff in preparation of food items, setting up assigned station in compliance with standards set by Chef. A s a Boyne Mountain team member, there are so many awesome perks for you to take advantage of, such as: ski passes, golf passes, waterpark passes, and discounts for food, beverages, retail, daycare, and so much more! To learn more about Boyne Mountain Resort, employment perks, and employee testimonials, click here - Boyne Mountain Employment !</br></br>"Work Where You Love To Play!" at Boyne Mountain Resort.</br></br>
<b>Responsibilities</b></br></br>The 
<strong>Line Cook's </strong>typical job functions include: </br>
<ul>
 <li> Preparing food according to food handling guidelines and cooking procedures</li>
 <li> Measuring and mixing ingredients according to recipe or use record to prepare and prep food items</li>
 <li> Stocking and maintaining sufficient levels of food products at line stations to assure a smooth service period</li>
 <li> Communicating and coordinating production with other cooks, wait staff and members of the food and beverage team</li>
 <li> Possessing knowledge and/or become familiar with all kitchen equipment</li>
 <li> Adjusting thermostat controls to regulate temperature of ovens, broilers, grills, roasters, kettles, etc</li>
 <li> Observing and testing foods being cooked by tasting, smelling, and piercing with thermometer to determine proper preparation and cooking</li>
 <li> Plating and portioning food and maintain consistency according to presentation specifications, using records or specs</li>
 <li> Labeling, dating and rotating all stored food</li>
 <li> Performing closing procedures including equipment maintenance and shut off, cleaning, sanitation, and organization of kitchen, walk-in coolers, and all storage areas</li>
</ul></br></br>
<b>Qualifications</b></br></br>This position may for you if: </br>
<ul>
 <li> You are 18 years old </li>
 <li> You have achieved a high school diploma or general education degree (GED) </li>
 <li> You have previous kitchen experience </li>
 <li> You are available to work days, evenings, weekends and holidays </li>
</ul>]]></jobdescription_opt>
      <jobid>13819_9541-1afa411082397b5a2e499c33fbc4bd3b</jobid>
      <jobtitle>Line Cook | Beach House</jobtitle>
      <jobtype>FULL_TIME</jobtype>
      <location>Boyne City,MI,United States</location>
      <logo>https://dev-jbk-ai.s3.amazonaws.com/company-logos/d-uploads/1621582705622-Boyne_Resorts_Logo.png</logo>
      <occupationalcategory>35-2014.00,Cooks, Restaurant</occupationalcategory>
      <postalCode>49712</postalCode>
      <salary null="true" />
      <salaryEstimate null="true" />
      <sameas>https://boyneresorts.com/</sameas>
      <url>https://click.appcast.io/track/9gg4v9i?cs=jsq&amp;exch=1a&amp;jg=3t1b&amp;bid=SSAKDDdbKVFCOLsOsUlBHA==</url>
   </job>
   <job>
      <company>Boyne Resorts</company>
      <jobdescription_opt><![CDATA[<b>Overview</b></br></br>On-site daycare at an affordable cost for active team members!</br></br>Looking for a new career opportunity? Consider Boyne Highlands Resort in Harbor Springs. Sure, we offer free golf and ski passes for our team members, but we're more than just a free pass.</br></br>Working at Boyne Highlands Resort gives you an opportunity to grow with us while we embark on a very exciting transformation! </br></br> Working at our resort is about being welcomed in as a member of the Highlands family. On average, our team members have been employed with us for over 7 years - and many have started in an entry level position and flourished with continued career advancement opportunities. </br></br> Ready to join the Highlands family? Check out the details below!</br></br>
<strong> Our Website </strong></br></br>
<strong> BOYNE HIGHLANDS RESORT </strong> is a family-owned, four-season destination located in Harbor Springs, Michigan and established in 1963. With 435 skiable acres, Boyne Highlands is the largest ski area in the Lower Peninsula and also offers the highest vertical terrain and mile-long runs. The winter season also offers Zipline Adventures, cross country skiing, snowshoeing, fat tire snow biking, the Aonach Mor Moonlight Dinner, and much more. The summer season delights with 72 holes of championship golf, a par-3 course, spa, horseback trail rides, biking, scenic chairlift rides, Segway PT Tours , and The Young Americans Dinner Theatre. </br>
<b>Team Member Benefits</b></br></br>Our team members get to experience all that our resort has to offer. Team members immediately receive great benefits like: </br>
<ul>
 <li> 40% discount on food and beverages in our restaurants </li>
 <li> 30% discount on spa services Sunday-Thursday </li>
 <li> FREE golf &amp; ski season passes </li>
 <li> Discounted adventure center activities </li>
 <li> Discounts on lodging for self and friends and family </li>
 <li> Friends and family vouchers </li>
 <li> Discounts on retail </li>
 <li> Child Care on site (affordable) </li>
 <li> 401k Eligible Immediately </li>
 <li> Team Member site: team.boynehighlands.com </li>
 <li> And so much more! </li>
</ul></br></br>
<b>Responsibilities</b></br></br>
<b>Qualifications</b></br></br>Boyne Highlands Resort is seeking applicants who are dedicated and excited to work hard and play hard.</br></br>
<strong>Qualities that will help you be successful:</strong> </br>
<ul>
 <li> Have a passion for guest service and the hospitality industry </li>
 <li> Display a friendly attitude and an outgoing personality </li>
 <li> Works well in team environment and projects a teamwork mentaility </li>
 <li> Helpful and kind when working with others. </li>
</ul></br> 
<strong>Highlighted Positions</strong> </br> 
<strong>Lodging:</strong> See all of our employment opportunities here --&gt; See options here </br> Housekeepers </br> Room Inspectors </br> Public Area Attendants </br> Front Desk </br></br> Security </br></br> 
<strong>Food and Beverage</strong> : </br></br> Line and Prep Cooks</br>Dishwashers </br> Hosts </br></br> Food Server/Bartender </br> Service Support]]></jobdescription_opt>
      <jobid>13819_9651-d3050553bc89d621be834bb2dc84ae04</jobid>
      <jobtitle>Ignite The Adventure at Boyne Highlands Resort - Landing Page</jobtitle>
      <jobtype>FULL_TIME</jobtype>
      <location>Conway,MI,United States</location>
      <logo>https://dev-jbk-ai.s3.amazonaws.com/company-logos/d-uploads/1621582705622-Boyne_Resorts_Logo.png</logo>
      <occupationalcategory />
      <postalCode>49722</postalCode>
      <salary null="true" />
      <salaryEstimate null="true" />
      <sameas>https://boyneresorts.com/</sameas>
      <url>https://click.appcast.io/track/97q2zil?cs=jsq&amp;exch=1a&amp;jg=3t1a&amp;bid=SSAKDDdbKVFCOLsOsUlBHA==</url>
   </job>
   <job>
      <company>Boyne Resorts</company>
      <jobdescription_opt><![CDATA[<b>Overview</b></br></br>As a 
<strong>Line Cook </strong>you are responsible for preparing food, helping the kitchen staff in preparation of food items, setting up assigned station in compliance with standards set by Chef. A s a Boyne Mountain team member, there are so many awesome perks for you to take advantage of, such as: ski passes, golf passes, waterpark passes, and discounts for food, beverages, retail, daycare, and so much more! To learn more about Boyne Mountain Resort, employment perks, and employee testimonials, click here - Boyne Mountain Employment !</br></br>"Work Where You Love To Play!" at Boyne Mountain Resort.</br></br>
<b>Responsibilities</b></br></br>The 
<strong>Line Cook's </strong>typical job functions include: </br>
<ul>
 <li> Preparing food according to food handling guidelines and cooking procedures</li>
 <li> Measuring and mixing ingredients according to recipe or use record to prepare and prep food items</li>
 <li> Stocking and maintaining sufficient levels of food products at line stations to assure a smooth service period</li>
 <li> Communicating and coordinating production with other cooks, wait staff and members of the food and beverage team</li>
 <li> Possessing knowledge and/or become familiar with all kitchen equipment</li>
 <li> Adjusting thermostat controls to regulate temperature of ovens, broilers, grills, roasters, kettles, etc</li>
 <li> Observing and testing foods being cooked by tasting, smelling, and piercing with thermometer to determine proper preparation and cooking</li>
 <li> Plating and portioning food and maintain consistency according to presentation specifications, using records or specs</li>
 <li> Labeling, dating and rotating all stored food</li>
 <li> Performing closing procedures including equipment maintenance and shut off, cleaning, sanitation, and organization of kitchen, walk-in coolers, and all storage areas</li>
</ul></br></br>
<b>Qualifications</b></br></br>This position may for you if: </br>
<ul>
 <li> You are 18 years old </li>
 <li> You have achieved a high school diploma or general education degree (GED) </li>
 <li> You have previous kitchen experience </li>
 <li> You are available to work days, evenings, weekends and holidays </li>
</ul>]]></jobdescription_opt>
      <jobid>13819_9541-ce78c57c60f3043225d280715147c6b5</jobid>
      <jobtitle>Line Cook | Beach House</jobtitle>
      <jobtype>FULL_TIME</jobtype>
      <location>Rapid City,MI,United States</location>
      <logo>https://dev-jbk-ai.s3.amazonaws.com/company-logos/d-uploads/1621582705622-Boyne_Resorts_Logo.png</logo>
      <occupationalcategory>35-2014.00,Cooks, Restaurant</occupationalcategory>
      <postalCode>49676</postalCode>
      <salary null="true" />
      <salaryEstimate null="true" />
      <sameas>https://boyneresorts.com/</sameas>
      <url>https://click.appcast.io/track/9gg4v6b?cs=jsq&amp;exch=1a&amp;jg=3t1b&amp;bid=SSAKDDdbKVFCOLsOsUlBHA==</url>
   </job>
   <job>
      <company>Boyne Resorts</company>
      <jobdescription_opt><![CDATA[<b>Overview</b></br></br>As a 
<strong>Dishwasher </strong>you are responsible for keeping dish area, restaurant equipment and utensils in clean and orderly condition. As a Boyne Mountain team member, there are so many awesome perks for you to take advantage of, such as: ski passes, golf passes, waterpark passes, and discounts for food, beverages, retail, daycare, and so much more! To learn more about Boyne Mountain Resort, employment perks, and employee testimonials, click here - Boyne Mountain Employment !</br></br>"Work Where You Love To Play!" at Boyne Mountain Resort.</br></br>
<b>Responsibilities</b></br></br>The
<strong> Dishwasher's </strong>typical job functions include: </br>
<ul>
 <li> Rinsing, scrubbing and scraping food from all dirty dishes, silverware, and cookware and washing them by hand or place them in racks or on conveyor to dish washing machine</li>
 <li> Placing all clean dishes in proper storage areas</li>
 <li> Cleaning and maintaining work areas, equipment and utensils</li>
 <li> Removing garbage and place refuse in designated pickup area</li>
 <li> Cleaning drains, disposals and sinks to ensure proper drainage</li>
 <li> Following all health regulations and assisting in maintaining a sanitary environment</li>
 <li> Setting up dish machine and ensuring machine is operating properly</li>
 <li> Sweeping and moping kitchen floors</li>
 <li> Washing worktables, walls, refrigerators and other kitchen surfaces</li>
</ul></br></br>
<b>Qualifications</b></br></br>This position may be for you if: </br>
<ul>
 <li> You are at least 16 years old </li>
 <li> You are available to work days, evenings, weekends and holidays </li>
 <li> You are able to lift up to 25 pounds </li>
 <li> You are able to stand for long periods of time </li>
</ul>]]></jobdescription_opt>
      <jobid>13819_9518-ce78c57c60f3043225d280715147c6b5</jobid>
      <jobtitle>Dishwasher | Everett's</jobtitle>
      <jobtype>FULL_TIME</jobtype>
      <location>Rapid City,MI,United States</location>
      <logo>https://dev-jbk-ai.s3.amazonaws.com/company-logos/d-uploads/1621582705622-Boyne_Resorts_Logo.png</logo>
      <occupationalcategory>35-9021.00,Dishwashers</occupationalcategory>
      <postalCode>49676</postalCode>
      <salary null="true" />
      <salaryEstimate null="true" />
      <sameas>https://boyneresorts.com/</sameas>
      <url>https://click.appcast.io/track/9gg4v94?cs=jsq&amp;exch=1a&amp;jg=3t1b&amp;bid=SSAKDDdbKVFCOLsOsUlBHA==</url>
   </job>
   <job>
      <company>Boyne Resorts</company>
      <jobdescription_opt><![CDATA[<b>Overview</b></br></br>As a 
<strong>Line Cook </strong>you are responsible for preparing food, helping the kitchen staff in preparation of food items, setting up assigned station in compliance with standards set by Chef. As a Boyne Mountain team member, there are so many awesome perks for you to take advantage of, such as: ski passes, golf passes, waterpark passes, and discounts for food, beverages, retail, daycare, and so much more! To learn more about Boyne Mountain Resort, employment perks, and employee testimonials, click here - Boyne Mountain Employment !</br></br>"Work Where You Love To Play!" at Boyne Mountain Resort.</br></br>
<b>Responsibilities</b></br></br>The 
<strong>Line Cook's </strong>typical job functions include: </br>
<ul>
 <li> Preparing food according to food handling guidelines and cooking procedures</li>
 <li> Measuring and mixing ingredients according to recipe or use record to prepare and prep food items</li>
 <li> Stocking and maintaining sufficient levels of food products at line stations to assure a smooth service period</li>
 <li> Communicating and coordinating production with other cooks, wait staff and members of the food and beverage team</li>
 <li> Possessing knowledge and/or become familiar with all kitchen equipment</li>
 <li> Adjusting thermostat controls to regulate temperature of ovens, broilers, grills, roasters, kettles, etc</li>
 <li> Observing and testing foods being cooked by tasting, smelling, and piercing with thermometer to determine proper preparation and cooking</li>
 <li> Plating and portioning food and maintain consistency according to presentation specifications, using records or specs</li>
 <li> Labeling, dating and rotating all stored food</li>
 <li> Performing closing procedures including equipment maintenance and shut off, cleaning, sanitation, and organization of kitchen, walk-in coolers, and all storage areas</li>
</ul></br></br>
<b>Qualifications</b></br></br>This position may for you if: </br>
<ul>
 <li> You are 18 years old </li>
 <li> You have achieved a high school diploma or general education degree (GED) </li>
 <li> You have previous kitchen experience </li>
 <li> You are available to work days, evenings, weekends and holidays </li>
</ul>]]></jobdescription_opt>
      <jobid>13819_9519-ce78c57c60f3043225d280715147c6b5</jobid>
      <jobtitle>Line Cook | Everett's</jobtitle>
      <jobtype>FULL_TIME</jobtype>
      <location>Rapid City,MI,United States</location>
      <logo>https://dev-jbk-ai.s3.amazonaws.com/company-logos/d-uploads/1621582705622-Boyne_Resorts_Logo.png</logo>
      <occupationalcategory>35-2014.00,Cooks, Restaurant</occupationalcategory>
      <postalCode>49676</postalCode>
      <salary null="true" />
      <salaryEstimate null="true" />
      <sameas>https://boyneresorts.com/</sameas>
      <url>https://click.appcast.io/track/9gg4v59?cs=jsq&amp;exch=1a&amp;jg=3t1b&amp;bid=SSAKDDdbKVFCOLsOsUlBHA==</url>
   </job>
   <job>
      <company>Boyne Resorts</company>
      <jobdescription_opt><![CDATA[<b>Overview</b></br></br>As a 
<strong>Line Cook </strong>you are responsible for preparing food, helping the kitchen staff in preparation of food items, setting up assigned station in compliance with standards set by Chef. As a Boyne Mountain team member, there are so many awesome perks for you to take advantage of, such as: ski passes, golf passes, waterpark passes, and discounts for food, beverages, retail, daycare, and so much more! To learn more about Boyne Mountain Resort, employment perks, and employee testimonials, click here - Boyne Mountain Employment !</br></br>"Work Where You Love To Play!" at Boyne Mountain Resort.</br></br>
<b>Responsibilities</b></br></br>The 
<strong>Line Cook's </strong>typical job functions include: </br>
<ul>
 <li> Preparing food according to food handling guidelines and cooking procedures</li>
 <li> Measuring and mixing ingredients according to recipe or use record to prepare and prep food items</li>
 <li> Stocking and maintaining sufficient levels of food products at line stations to assure a smooth service period</li>
 <li> Communicating and coordinating production with other cooks, wait staff and members of the food and beverage team</li>
 <li> Possessing knowledge and/or become familiar with all kitchen equipment</li>
 <li> Adjusting thermostat controls to regulate temperature of ovens, broilers, grills, roasters, kettles, etc</li>
 <li> Observing and testing foods being cooked by tasting, smelling, and piercing with thermometer to determine proper preparation and cooking</li>
 <li> Plating and portioning food and maintain consistency according to presentation specifications, using records or specs</li>
 <li> Labeling, dating and rotating all stored food</li>
 <li> Performing closing procedures including equipment maintenance and shut off, cleaning, sanitation, and organization of kitchen, walk-in coolers, and all storage areas</li>
</ul></br></br>
<b>Qualifications</b></br></br>This position may for you if: </br>
<ul>
 <li> You are 18 years old </li>
 <li> You have achieved a high school diploma or general education degree (GED) </li>
 <li> You have previous kitchen experience </li>
 <li> You are available to work days, evenings, weekends and holidays </li>
</ul>]]></jobdescription_opt>
      <jobid>13819_9519-5b21a5a6637959bdcd9f585d877d760e</jobid>
      <jobtitle>Line Cook | Everett's</jobtitle>
      <jobtype>FULL_TIME</jobtype>
      <location>Wolverine,MI,United States</location>
      <logo>https://dev-jbk-ai.s3.amazonaws.com/company-logos/d-uploads/1621582705622-Boyne_Resorts_Logo.png</logo>
      <occupationalcategory>35-2014.00,Cooks, Restaurant</occupationalcategory>
      <postalCode>49799</postalCode>
      <salary null="true" />
      <salaryEstimate null="true" />
      <sameas>https://boyneresorts.com/</sameas>
      <url>https://click.appcast.io/track/9gg4v30?cs=jsq&amp;exch=1a&amp;jg=3t1b&amp;bid=SSAKDDdbKVFCOLsOsUlBHA==</url>
   </job>
   <job>
      <company>Boyne Resorts</company>
      <jobdescription_opt><![CDATA[<b>Overview</b></br></br>As a 
<strong>Dishwasher </strong>you are responsible for keeping dish area, restaurant equipment and utensils in clean and orderly condition. As a Boyne Mountain team member, there are so many awesome perks for you to take advantage of, such as: ski passes, golf passes, waterpark passes, and discounts for food, beverages, retail, daycare, and so much more! To learn more about Boyne Mountain Resort, employment perks, and employee testimonials, click here - Boyne Mountain Employment !</br></br>"Work Where You Love To Play!" at Boyne Mountain Resort.</br></br>
<b>Responsibilities</b></br></br>The 
<strong>Dishwasher's </strong>typical job functions include: </br>
<ul>
 <li> Rinsing, scrubbing and scraping food from all dirty dishes, silverware, and cookware and washing them by hand or place them in racks or on conveyor to dishwashing machine</li>
 <li> Placing all clean dishes in proper storage areas</li>
 <li> Cleaning and maintaining work areas, equipment and utensils</li>
 <li> Removing garbage and place refuse in designated pickup area</li>
 <li> Cleaning drains, disposals and sinks to ensure proper drainage</li>
 <li> Following all health regulations and assisting in maintaining a sanitary environment</li>
 <li> Setting up dish machine and ensuring machine is operating properly</li>
 <li> Sweeping and moping kitchen floors</li>
 <li> Washing worktables, walls, refrigerators and other kitchen surfaces</li>
</ul></br></br>
<b>Qualifications</b></br></br>This position may be for you if: </br>
<ul>
 <li> You are at least 16 years old </li>
 <li> You are available to work days, evenings, weekends and holidays </li>
 <li> You are able to lift up to 25 pounds </li>
 <li> You are able to stand for long periods of time </li>
</ul>]]></jobdescription_opt>
      <jobid>13819_9540-f8576777f875bf2f904de3d02329fcbd</jobid>
      <jobtitle>Dishwasher | Beach House</jobtitle>
      <jobtype>FULL_TIME</jobtype>
      <location>Pellston,MI,United States</location>
      <logo>https://dev-jbk-ai.s3.amazonaws.com/company-logos/d-uploads/1621582705622-Boyne_Resorts_Logo.png</logo>
      <occupationalcategory />
      <postalCode>49769</postalCode>
      <salary null="true" />
      <salaryEstimate null="true" />
      <sameas>https://boyneresorts.com/</sameas>
      <url>https://click.appcast.io/track/9gg4v7a?cs=jsq&amp;exch=1a&amp;jg=3t1b&amp;bid=SSAKDDdbKVFCOLsOsUlBHA==</url>
   </job>
   <job>
      <company>Boyne Resorts</company>
      <jobdescription_opt><![CDATA[<b>Overview</b></br></br>On-site daycare at an affordable cost for active team members!</br></br>Looking for a new career opportunity? Consider Boyne Highlands Resort in Harbor Springs. Sure, we offer free golf and ski passes for our team members, but we're more than just a free pass.</br></br>Working at Boyne Highlands Resort gives you an opportunity to grow with us while we embark on a very exciting transformation! </br></br> Working at our resort is about being welcomed in as a member of the Highlands family. On average, our team members have been employed with us for over 7 years - and many have started in an entry level position and flourished with continued career advancement opportunities. </br></br> Ready to join the Highlands family? Check out the details below!</br></br>
<strong> Our Website </strong></br></br>
<strong> BOYNE HIGHLANDS RESORT </strong> is a family-owned, four-season destination located in Harbor Springs, Michigan and established in 1963. With 435 skiable acres, Boyne Highlands is the largest ski area in the Lower Peninsula and also offers the highest vertical terrain and mile-long runs. The winter season also offers Zipline Adventures, cross country skiing, snowshoeing, fat tire snow biking, the Aonach Mor Moonlight Dinner, and much more. The summer season delights with 72 holes of championship golf, a par-3 course, spa, horseback trail rides, biking, scenic chairlift rides, Segway PT Tours , and The Young Americans Dinner Theatre. </br>
<b>Team Member Benefits</b></br></br>Our team members get to experience all that our resort has to offer. Team members immediately receive great benefits like: </br>
<ul>
 <li> 40% discount on food and beverages in our restaurants </li>
 <li> 30% discount on spa services Sunday-Thursday </li>
 <li> FREE golf &amp; ski season passes </li>
 <li> Discounted adventure center activities </li>
 <li> Discounts on lodging for self and friends and family </li>
 <li> Friends and family vouchers </li>
 <li> Discounts on retail </li>
 <li> Child Care on site (affordable) </li>
 <li> 401k Eligible Immediately </li>
 <li> Team Member site: team.boynehighlands.com </li>
 <li> And so much more! </li>
</ul></br></br>
<b>Responsibilities</b></br></br>
<b>Qualifications</b></br></br>Boyne Highlands Resort is seeking applicants who are dedicated and excited to work hard and play hard.</br></br>
<strong>Qualities that will help you be successful:</strong> </br>
<ul>
 <li> Have a passion for guest service and the hospitality industry </li>
 <li> Display a friendly attitude and an outgoing personality </li>
 <li> Works well in team environment and projects a teamwork mentaility </li>
 <li> Helpful and kind when working with others. </li>
</ul></br> 
<strong>Highlighted Positions</strong> </br> 
<strong>Lodging:</strong> See all of our employment opportunities here --&gt; See options here </br> Housekeepers </br> Room Inspectors </br> Public Area Attendants </br> Front Desk </br></br> Security </br></br> 
<strong>Food and Beverage</strong> : </br></br> Line and Prep Cooks</br>Dishwashers </br> Hosts </br></br> Food Server/Bartender </br> Service Support]]></jobdescription_opt>
      <jobid>13819_9651-9c191ebd16d38898cf2e92348d2c0c76</jobid>
      <jobtitle>Ignite The Adventure at Boyne Highlands Resort - Landing Page</jobtitle>
      <jobtype>FULL_TIME</jobtype>
      <location>Omena,MI,United States</location>
      <logo>https://dev-jbk-ai.s3.amazonaws.com/company-logos/d-uploads/1621582705622-Boyne_Resorts_Logo.png</logo>
      <occupationalcategory />
      <postalCode>49674</postalCode>
      <salary null="true" />
      <salaryEstimate null="true" />
      <sameas>https://boyneresorts.com/</sameas>
      <url>https://click.appcast.io/track/9oqkz0m?cs=jsq&amp;exch=1a&amp;jg=3t1a&amp;bid=SSAKDDdbKVFCOLsOsUlBHA==</url>
   </job>
   <job>
      <company>Boyne Resorts</company>
      <jobdescription_opt><![CDATA[<b>Overview</b></br></br>On-site daycare at an affordable cost for active team members!</br></br>Looking for a new career opportunity? Consider Boyne Highlands Resort in Harbor Springs. Sure, we offer free golf and ski passes for our team members, but we're more than just a free pass.</br></br>Working at Boyne Highlands Resort gives you an opportunity to grow with us while we embark on a very exciting transformation! </br></br> Working at our resort is about being welcomed in as a member of the Highlands family. On average, our team members have been employed with us for over 7 years - and many have started in an entry level position and flourished with continued career advancement opportunities. </br></br> Ready to join the Highlands family? Check out the details below!</br></br>
<strong> Our Website </strong></br></br>
<strong> BOYNE HIGHLANDS RESORT </strong> is a family-owned, four-season destination located in Harbor Springs, Michigan and established in 1963. With 435 skiable acres, Boyne Highlands is the largest ski area in the Lower Peninsula and also offers the highest vertical terrain and mile-long runs. The winter season also offers Zipline Adventures, cross country skiing, snowshoeing, fat tire snow biking, the Aonach Mor Moonlight Dinner, and much more. The summer season delights with 72 holes of championship golf, a par-3 course, spa, horseback trail rides, biking, scenic chairlift rides, Segway PT Tours , and The Young Americans Dinner Theatre. </br>
<b>Team Member Benefits</b></br></br>Our team members get to experience all that our resort has to offer. Team members immediately receive great benefits like: </br>
<ul>
 <li> 40% discount on food and beverages in our restaurants </li>
 <li> 30% discount on spa services Sunday-Thursday </li>
 <li> FREE golf &amp; ski season passes </li>
 <li> Discounted adventure center activities </li>
 <li> Discounts on lodging for self and friends and family </li>
 <li> Friends and family vouchers </li>
 <li> Discounts on retail </li>
 <li> Child Care on site (affordable) </li>
 <li> 401k Eligible Immediately </li>
 <li> Team Member site: team.boynehighlands.com </li>
 <li> And so much more! </li>
</ul></br></br>
<b>Responsibilities</b></br></br>
<b>Qualifications</b></br></br>Boyne Highlands Resort is seeking applicants who are dedicated and excited to work hard and play hard.</br></br>
<strong>Qualities that will help you be successful:</strong> </br>
<ul>
 <li> Have a passion for guest service and the hospitality industry </li>
 <li> Display a friendly attitude and an outgoing personality </li>
 <li> Works well in team environment and projects a teamwork mentaility </li>
 <li> Helpful and kind when working with others. </li>
</ul></br> 
<strong>Highlighted Positions</strong> </br> 
<strong>Lodging:</strong> See all of our employment opportunities here --&gt; See options here </br> Housekeepers </br> Room Inspectors </br> Public Area Attendants </br> Front Desk </br></br> Security </br></br> 
<strong>Food and Beverage</strong> : </br></br> Line and Prep Cooks</br>Dishwashers </br> Hosts </br></br> Food Server/Bartender </br> Service Support]]></jobdescription_opt>
      <jobid>13819_9651</jobid>
      <jobtitle>Ignite The Adventure at Boyne Highlands Resort - Landing Page</jobtitle>
      <jobtype>FULL_TIME</jobtype>
      <location>Harbor Springs,MI,United States</location>
      <logo>https://dev-jbk-ai.s3.amazonaws.com/company-logos/d-uploads/1621582705622-Boyne_Resorts_Logo.png</logo>
      <occupationalcategory />
      <postalCode>49740</postalCode>
      <salary null="true" />
      <salaryEstimate null="true" />
      <sameas>https://boyneresorts.com/</sameas>
      <url>https://click.appcast.io/track/92v1bak?cs=jsq&amp;exch=1a&amp;jg=3t1a&amp;bid=SSAKDDdbKVFCOLsOsUlBHA==</url>
   </job>
   <job>
      <company>Boyne Resorts</company>
      <jobdescription_opt><![CDATA[<b>Overview</b></br></br>As a 
<strong>Dishwasher </strong>you are responsible for keeping dish area, restaurant equipment and utensils in clean and orderly condition. As a Boyne Mountain team member, there are so many awesome perks for you to take advantage of, such as: ski passes, golf passes, waterpark passes, and discounts for food, beverages, retail, daycare, and so much more! To learn more about Boyne Mountain Resort, employment perks, and employee testimonials, click here - Boyne Mountain Employment !</br></br>"Work Where You Love To Play!" at Boyne Mountain Resort.</br></br>
<b>Responsibilities</b></br></br>The 
<strong>Dishwasher's </strong>typical job functions include: </br>
<ul>
 <li> Rinsing, scrubbing and scraping food from all dirty dishes, silverware, and cookware and washing them by hand or place them in racks or on conveyor to dishwashing machine</li>
 <li> Placing all clean dishes in proper storage areas</li>
 <li> Cleaning and maintaining work areas, equipment and utensils</li>
 <li> Removing garbage and place refuse in designated pickup area</li>
 <li> Cleaning drains, disposals and sinks to ensure proper drainage</li>
 <li> Following all health regulations and assisting in maintaining a sanitary environment</li>
 <li> Setting up dish machine and ensuring machine is operating properly</li>
 <li> Sweeping and moping kitchen floors</li>
 <li> Washing worktables, walls, refrigerators and other kitchen surfaces</li>
</ul></br></br>
<b>Qualifications</b></br></br>This position may be for you if: </br>
<ul>
 <li> You are at least 16 years old </li>
 <li> You are available to work days, evenings, weekends and holidays </li>
 <li> You are able to lift up to 25 pounds </li>
 <li> You are able to stand for long periods of time </li>
</ul>]]></jobdescription_opt>
      <jobid>13819_9540-9d4f6d269bb3c951a562eee42efa731c</jobid>
      <jobtitle>Dishwasher | Beach House</jobtitle>
      <jobtype>FULL_TIME</jobtype>
      <location>Petoskey,MI,United States</location>
      <logo>https://dev-jbk-ai.s3.amazonaws.com/company-logos/d-uploads/1621582705622-Boyne_Resorts_Logo.png</logo>
      <occupationalcategory />
      <postalCode>49770</postalCode>
      <salary null="true" />
      <salaryEstimate null="true" />
      <sameas>https://boyneresorts.com/</sameas>
      <url>https://click.appcast.io/track/9gg4v3y?cs=jsq&amp;exch=1a&amp;jg=3t1b&amp;bid=SSAKDDdbKVFCOLsOsUlBHA==</url>
   </job>
   <job>
      <company>Boyne Resorts</company>
      <jobdescription_opt><![CDATA[<b>Overview</b></br></br>As a 
<strong>Dishwasher </strong>you are responsible for keeping dish area, restaurant equipment and utensils in clean and orderly condition. As a Boyne Mountain team member, there are so many awesome perks for you to take advantage of, such as: ski passes, golf passes, waterpark passes, and discounts for food, beverages, retail, daycare, and so much more! To learn more about Boyne Mountain Resort, employment perks, and employee testimonials, click here - Boyne Mountain Employment !</br></br>"Work Where You Love To Play!" at Boyne Mountain Resort.</br></br>
<b>Responsibilities</b></br></br>The 
<strong>Dishwasher's </strong>typical job functions include: </br>
<ul>
 <li> Rinsing, scrubbing and scraping food from all dirty dishes, silverware, and cookware and washing them by hand or place them in racks or on conveyor to dishwashing machine</li>
 <li> Placing all clean dishes in proper storage areas</li>
 <li> Cleaning and maintaining work areas, equipment and utensils</li>
 <li> Removing garbage and place refuse in designated pickup area</li>
 <li> Cleaning drains, disposals and sinks to ensure proper drainage</li>
 <li> Following all health regulations and assisting in maintaining a sanitary environment</li>
 <li> Setting up dish machine and ensuring machine is operating properly</li>
 <li> Sweeping and moping kitchen floors</li>
 <li> Washing worktables, walls, refrigerators and other kitchen surfaces</li>
</ul></br></br>
<b>Qualifications</b></br></br>This position may be for you if: </br>
<ul>
 <li> You are at least 16 years old </li>
 <li> You are available to work days, evenings, weekends and holidays </li>
 <li> You are able to lift up to 25 pounds </li>
 <li> You are able to stand for long periods of time </li>
</ul>]]></jobdescription_opt>
      <jobid>13819_9540-63db3ba2386ef041eaa95ed2b8836f80</jobid>
      <jobtitle>Dishwasher | Beach House</jobtitle>
      <jobtype>FULL_TIME</jobtype>
      <location>Harbor Springs,MI,United States</location>
      <logo>https://dev-jbk-ai.s3.amazonaws.com/company-logos/d-uploads/1621582705622-Boyne_Resorts_Logo.png</logo>
      <occupationalcategory />
      <postalCode>49740</postalCode>
      <salary null="true" />
      <salaryEstimate null="true" />
      <sameas>https://boyneresorts.com/</sameas>
      <url>https://click.appcast.io/track/9gg4v5a?cs=jsq&amp;exch=1a&amp;jg=3t1b&amp;bid=SSAKDDdbKVFCOLsOsUlBHA==</url>
   </job>
   <job>
      <company>Boyne Resorts</company>
      <jobdescription_opt><![CDATA[<b>Overview</b></br></br>As a 
<strong>Dishwasher </strong>you are responsible for keeping dish area, restaurant equipment and utensils in clean and orderly condition. As a Boyne Mountain team member, there are so many awesome perks for you to take advantage of, such as: ski passes, golf passes, waterpark passes, and discounts for food, beverages, retail, daycare, and so much more! To learn more about Boyne Mountain Resort, employment perks, and employee testimonials, click here - Boyne Mountain Employment !</br></br>"Work Where You Love To Play!" at Boyne Mountain Resort.</br></br>
<b>Responsibilities</b></br></br>The
<strong> Dishwasher's </strong>typical job functions include: </br>
<ul>
 <li> Rinsing, scrubbing and scraping food from all dirty dishes, silverware, and cookware and washing them by hand or place them in racks or on conveyor to dish washing machine</li>
 <li> Placing all clean dishes in proper storage areas</li>
 <li> Cleaning and maintaining work areas, equipment and utensils</li>
 <li> Removing garbage and place refuse in designated pickup area</li>
 <li> Cleaning drains, disposals and sinks to ensure proper drainage</li>
 <li> Following all health regulations and assisting in maintaining a sanitary environment</li>
 <li> Setting up dish machine and ensuring machine is operating properly</li>
 <li> Sweeping and moping kitchen floors</li>
 <li> Washing worktables, walls, refrigerators and other kitchen surfaces</li>
</ul></br></br>
<b>Qualifications</b></br></br>This position may be for you if: </br>
<ul>
 <li> You are at least 16 years old </li>
 <li> You are available to work days, evenings, weekends and holidays </li>
 <li> You are able to lift up to 25 pounds </li>
 <li> You are able to stand for long periods of time </li>
</ul>]]></jobdescription_opt>
      <jobid>13819_9518-aa569cae1e44fa56091a82ef9ecea0e9</jobid>
      <jobtitle>Dishwasher | Everett's</jobtitle>
      <jobtype>FULL_TIME</jobtype>
      <location>Bay Shore,MI,United States</location>
      <logo>https://dev-jbk-ai.s3.amazonaws.com/company-logos/d-uploads/1621582705622-Boyne_Resorts_Logo.png</logo>
      <occupationalcategory>35-9021.00,Dishwashers</occupationalcategory>
      <postalCode>49711</postalCode>
      <salary null="true" />
      <salaryEstimate null="true" />
      <sameas>https://boyneresorts.com/</sameas>
      <url>https://click.appcast.io/track/9gg4v32?cs=jsq&amp;exch=1a&amp;jg=3t1b&amp;bid=SSAKDDdbKVFCOLsOsUlBHA==</url>
   </job>
   <job>
      <company>Boyne Resorts</company>
      <jobdescription_opt><![CDATA[<b>Overview</b></br></br>As a 
<strong>Dishwasher </strong>you are responsible for keeping dish area, restaurant equipment and utensils in clean and orderly condition. As a Boyne Mountain team member, there are so many awesome perks for you to take advantage of, such as: ski passes, golf passes, waterpark passes, and discounts for food, beverages, retail, daycare, and so much more! To learn more about Boyne Mountain Resort, employment perks, and employee testimonials, click here - Boyne Mountain Employment !</br></br>"Work Where You Love To Play!" at Boyne Mountain Resort.</br></br>
<b>Responsibilities</b></br></br>The 
<strong>Dishwasher's </strong>typical job functions include: </br>
<ul>
 <li> Rinsing, scrubbing and scraping food from all dirty dishes, silverware, and cookware and washing them by hand or place them in racks or on conveyor to dishwashing machine</li>
 <li> Placing all clean dishes in proper storage areas</li>
 <li> Cleaning and maintaining work areas, equipment and utensils</li>
 <li> Removing garbage and place refuse in designated pickup area</li>
 <li> Cleaning drains, disposals and sinks to ensure proper drainage</li>
 <li> Following all health regulations and assisting in maintaining a sanitary environment</li>
 <li> Setting up dish machine and ensuring machine is operating properly</li>
 <li> Sweeping and moping kitchen floors</li>
 <li> Washing worktables, walls, refrigerators and other kitchen surfaces</li>
</ul></br></br>
<b>Qualifications</b></br></br>This position may be for you if: </br>
<ul>
 <li> You are at least 16 years old </li>
 <li> You are available to work days, evenings, weekends and holidays </li>
 <li> You are able to lift up to 25 pounds </li>
 <li> You are able to stand for long periods of time </li>
</ul>]]></jobdescription_opt>
      <jobid>13819_9544</jobid>
      <jobtitle>Banquet Dishwasher</jobtitle>
      <jobtype>FULL_TIME</jobtype>
      <location>Boyne Falls,MI,United States</location>
      <logo>https://dev-jbk-ai.s3.amazonaws.com/company-logos/d-uploads/1621582705622-Boyne_Resorts_Logo.png</logo>
      <occupationalcategory>35-9021.00,Dishwashers</occupationalcategory>
      <postalCode>49713</postalCode>
      <salary null="true" />
      <salaryEstimate null="true" />
      <sameas>https://boyneresorts.com/</sameas>
      <url>https://click.appcast.io/track/92v1bb7?cs=jsq&amp;exch=1a&amp;jg=3t1b&amp;bid=SSAKDDdbKVFCOLsOsUlBHA==</url>
   </job>
   <job>
      <company>Boyne Resorts</company>
      <jobdescription_opt><![CDATA[<b>Overview</b></br></br>As a 
<strong>Dishwasher </strong>you are responsible for keeping dish area, restaurant equipment and utensils in clean and orderly condition. As a Boyne Mountain team member, there are so many awesome perks for you to take advantage of, such as: ski passes, golf passes, waterpark passes, and discounts for food, beverages, retail, daycare, and so much more! To learn more about Boyne Mountain Resort, employment perks, and employee testimonials, click here - Boyne Mountain Employment !</br></br>"Work Where You Love To Play!" at Boyne Mountain Resort.</br></br>
<b>Responsibilities</b></br></br>The 
<strong>Dishwasher's </strong>typical job functions include: </br>
<ul>
 <li> Rinsing, scrubbing and scraping food from all dirty dishes, silverware, and cookware and washing them by hand or place them in racks or on conveyor to dishwashing machine</li>
 <li> Placing all clean dishes in proper storage areas</li>
 <li> Cleaning and maintaining work areas, equipment and utensils</li>
 <li> Removing garbage and place refuse in designated pickup area</li>
 <li> Cleaning drains, disposals and sinks to ensure proper drainage</li>
 <li> Following all health regulations and assisting in maintaining a sanitary environment</li>
 <li> Setting up dish machine and ensuring machine is operating properly</li>
 <li> Sweeping and moping kitchen floors</li>
 <li> Washing worktables, walls, refrigerators and other kitchen surfaces</li>
</ul></br></br>
<b>Qualifications</b></br></br>This position may be for you if: </br>
<ul>
 <li> You are at least 16 years old </li>
 <li> You are available to work days, evenings, weekends and holidays </li>
 <li> You are able to lift up to 25 pounds </li>
 <li> You are able to stand for long periods of time </li>
</ul>]]></jobdescription_opt>
      <jobid>13819_9540-ba97b6a7f9cc40249bcc4088ed19286f</jobid>
      <jobtitle>Dishwasher | Beach House</jobtitle>
      <jobtype>FULL_TIME</jobtype>
      <location>Eastport,MI,United States</location>
      <logo>https://dev-jbk-ai.s3.amazonaws.com/company-logos/d-uploads/1621582705622-Boyne_Resorts_Logo.png</logo>
      <occupationalcategory />
      <postalCode>49627</postalCode>
      <salary null="true" />
      <salaryEstimate null="true" />
      <sameas>https://boyneresorts.com/</sameas>
      <url>https://click.appcast.io/track/9gg4v6e?cs=jsq&amp;exch=1a&amp;jg=3t1b&amp;bid=SSAKDDdbKVFCOLsOsUlBHA==</url>
   </job>
   <job>
      <company>Boyne Resorts</company>
      <jobdescription_opt><![CDATA[<b>Overview</b></br></br>As a 
<strong>Banquet</strong>
<strong> Line Cook </strong>you are responsible for preparing food, helping the kitchen staff in preparation of food items, setting up assigned station in compliance with standards set by Cafeteria Chef. </br></br> As a Boyne Mountain team member, there are so many awesome perks for you to take advantage of, such as: ski passes, golf passes, waterpark passes, and discounts for food, beverages, retail, daycare, and so much more! To learn more about Boyne Mountain Resort, employment perks, and employee testimonials, click here - Boyne Mountain Employment !</br></br>"Work Where You Love To Play!" at Boyne Mountain Resort</br></br>
<b>Responsibilities</b></br></br>The 
<strong>Banquet</strong>
<strong> Line Cook's </strong>typical job functions include: </br>
<ul>
 <li> Preparing food according to food handling guidelines and cooking procedures</li>
 <li> Measuring and mixing ingredients according to recipe or use record to prepare and prep food items</li>
 <li> Stocking and maintaining sufficient levels of food products at line stations to assure a smooth service period</li>
 <li> Communicating and coordinating production with other cooks, wait staff and members of the food and beverage team</li>
 <li> Possessing knowledge and/or become familiar with all kitchen equipment</li>
 <li> Adjusting thermostat controls to regulate temperature of ovens, broilers, grills, roasters, kettles, etc</li>
 <li> Observing and testing foods being cooked by tasting, smelling, and piercing with thermometer to determine proper preparation and cooking</li>
 <li> Plating and portioning food and maintain consistency according to presentation specifications, using records or specs</li>
 <li> Labeling, dating and rotating all stored food</li>
 <li> Performing closing procedures including equipment maintenance and shut off, cleaning, sanitation, and organization of kitchen, walk-in coolers, and all storage areas</li>
</ul></br></br>
<b>Qualifications</b></br></br>This position may for you if: </br>
<ul>
 <li> You are 18 years old </li>
 <li> You have achieved a high school diploma or general education degree (GED) </li>
 <li> You have previous kitchen experience </li>
 <li> You are available to work days, evenings, weekends and holidays </li>
</ul>]]></jobdescription_opt>
      <jobid>13819_9533-63db3ba2386ef041eaa95ed2b8836f80</jobid>
      <jobtitle>Cook</jobtitle>
      <jobtype>FULL_TIME</jobtype>
      <location>Harbor Springs,MI,United States</location>
      <logo>https://dev-jbk-ai.s3.amazonaws.com/company-logos/d-uploads/1621582705622-Boyne_Resorts_Logo.png</logo>
      <occupationalcategory>35-2014.00,Cooks, Restaurant</occupationalcategory>
      <postalCode>49740</postalCode>
      <salary null="true" />
      <salaryEstimate null="true" />
      <sameas>https://boyneresorts.com/</sameas>
      <url>https://click.appcast.io/track/97qgopi?cs=jsq&amp;exch=1a&amp;jg=3t1a&amp;bid=SSAKDDdbKVFCOLsOsUlBHA==</url>
   </job>
   <job>
      <company>Boyne Resorts</company>
      <jobdescription_opt><![CDATA[<b>Overview</b></br></br>On-site daycare at an affordable cost for active team members!</br></br>Looking for a new career opportunity? Consider Boyne Highlands Resort in Harbor Springs. Sure, we offer free golf and ski passes for our team members, but we're more than just a free pass.</br></br>Working at Boyne Highlands Resort gives you an opportunity to grow with us while we embark on a very exciting transformation! </br></br> Working at our resort is about being welcomed in as a member of the Highlands family. On average, our team members have been employed with us for over 7 years - and many have started in an entry level position and flourished with continued career advancement opportunities. </br></br> Ready to join the Highlands family? Check out the details below!</br></br>
<strong> Our Website </strong></br></br>
<strong> BOYNE HIGHLANDS RESORT </strong> is a family-owned, four-season destination located in Harbor Springs, Michigan and established in 1963. With 435 skiable acres, Boyne Highlands is the largest ski area in the Lower Peninsula and also offers the highest vertical terrain and mile-long runs. The winter season also offers Zipline Adventures, cross country skiing, snowshoeing, fat tire snow biking, the Aonach Mor Moonlight Dinner, and much more. The summer season delights with 72 holes of championship golf, a par-3 course, spa, horseback trail rides, biking, scenic chairlift rides, Segway PT Tours , and The Young Americans Dinner Theatre. </br>
<b>Team Member Benefits</b></br></br>Our team members get to experience all that our resort has to offer. Team members immediately receive great benefits like: </br>
<ul>
 <li> 40% discount on food and beverages in our restaurants </li>
 <li> 30% discount on spa services Sunday-Thursday </li>
 <li> FREE golf &amp; ski season passes </li>
 <li> Discounted adventure center activities </li>
 <li> Discounts on lodging for self and friends and family </li>
 <li> Friends and family vouchers </li>
 <li> Discounts on retail </li>
 <li> Child Care on site (affordable) </li>
 <li> 401k Eligible Immediately </li>
 <li> Team Member site: team.boynehighlands.com </li>
 <li> And so much more! </li>
</ul></br></br>
<b>Responsibilities</b></br></br>
<b>Qualifications</b></br></br>Boyne Highlands Resort is seeking applicants who are dedicated and excited to work hard and play hard.</br></br>
<strong>Qualities that will help you be successful:</strong> </br>
<ul>
 <li> Have a passion for guest service and the hospitality industry </li>
 <li> Display a friendly attitude and an outgoing personality </li>
 <li> Works well in team environment and projects a teamwork mentaility </li>
 <li> Helpful and kind when working with others. </li>
</ul></br> 
<strong>Highlighted Positions</strong> </br> 
<strong>Lodging:</strong> See all of our employment opportunities here --&gt; See options here </br> Housekeepers </br> Room Inspectors </br> Public Area Attendants </br> Front Desk </br></br> Security </br></br> 
<strong>Food and Beverage</strong> : </br></br> Line and Prep Cooks</br>Dishwashers </br> Hosts </br></br> Food Server/Bartender </br> Service Support]]></jobdescription_opt>
      <jobid>13819_9651-659c08c98fc3d5b579a134b108d3e2ec</jobid>
      <jobtitle>Food and Beverage Staff</jobtitle>
      <jobtype>FULL_TIME</jobtype>
      <location>Harbor Springs,MI,United States</location>
      <logo>https://dev-jbk-ai.s3.amazonaws.com/company-logos/d-uploads/1621582705622-Boyne_Resorts_Logo.png</logo>
      <occupationalcategory>11-9051.00,Food Service Managers</occupationalcategory>
      <postalCode>49740</postalCode>
      <salary null="true" />
      <salaryEstimate null="true" />
      <sameas>https://boyneresorts.com/</sameas>
      <url>https://click.appcast.io/track/97qgopm?cs=jsq&amp;exch=1a&amp;jg=3t1a&amp;bid=SSAKDDdbKVFCOLsOsUlBHA==</url>
   </job>
   <job>
      <company>Boyne Resorts</company>
      <jobdescription_opt><![CDATA[<b>Overview</b></br></br>On-site daycare at an affordable cost for active team members!</br></br>Looking for a new career opportunity? Consider Boyne Highlands Resort in Harbor Springs. Sure, we offer free golf and ski passes for our team members, but we're more than just a free pass.</br></br>Working at Boyne Highlands Resort gives you an opportunity to grow with us while we embark on a very exciting transformation! </br></br> Working at our resort is about being welcomed in as a member of the Highlands family. On average, our team members have been employed with us for over 7 years - and many have started in an entry level position and flourished with continued career advancement opportunities. </br></br> Ready to join the Highlands family? Check out the details below!</br></br>
<strong> Our Website </strong></br></br>
<strong> BOYNE HIGHLANDS RESORT </strong> is a family-owned, four-season destination located in Harbor Springs, Michigan and established in 1963. With 435 skiable acres, Boyne Highlands is the largest ski area in the Lower Peninsula and also offers the highest vertical terrain and mile-long runs. The winter season also offers Zipline Adventures, cross country skiing, snowshoeing, fat tire snow biking, the Aonach Mor Moonlight Dinner, and much more. The summer season delights with 72 holes of championship golf, a par-3 course, spa, horseback trail rides, biking, scenic chairlift rides, Segway PT Tours , and The Young Americans Dinner Theatre. </br>
<b>Team Member Benefits</b></br></br>Our team members get to experience all that our resort has to offer. Team members immediately receive great benefits like: </br>
<ul>
 <li> 40% discount on food and beverages in our restaurants </li>
 <li> 30% discount on spa services Sunday-Thursday </li>
 <li> FREE golf &amp; ski season passes </li>
 <li> Discounted adventure center activities </li>
 <li> Discounts on lodging for self and friends and family </li>
 <li> Friends and family vouchers </li>
 <li> Discounts on retail </li>
 <li> Child Care on site (affordable) </li>
 <li> 401k Eligible Immediately </li>
 <li> Team Member site: team.boynehighlands.com </li>
 <li> And so much more! </li>
</ul></br></br>
<b>Responsibilities</b></br></br>
<b>Qualifications</b></br></br>Boyne Highlands Resort is seeking applicants who are dedicated and excited to work hard and play hard.</br></br>
<strong>Qualities that will help you be successful:</strong> </br>
<ul>
 <li> Have a passion for guest service and the hospitality industry </li>
 <li> Display a friendly attitude and an outgoing personality </li>
 <li> Works well in team environment and projects a teamwork mentaility </li>
 <li> Helpful and kind when working with others. </li>
</ul></br> 
<strong>Highlighted Positions</strong> </br> 
<strong>Lodging:</strong> See all of our employment opportunities here --&gt; See options here </br> Housekeepers </br> Room Inspectors </br> Public Area Attendants </br> Front Desk </br></br> Security </br></br> 
<strong>Food and Beverage</strong> : </br></br> Line and Prep Cooks</br>Dishwashers </br> Hosts </br></br> Food Server/Bartender </br> Service Support]]></jobdescription_opt>
      <jobid>13819_9651-4338ac4dbee8b0a8b0a06c952f735293</jobid>
      <jobtitle>Housekeepers Needed!</jobtitle>
      <jobtype>FULL_TIME</jobtype>
      <location>Harbor Springs,MI,United States</location>
      <logo>https://dev-jbk-ai.s3.amazonaws.com/company-logos/d-uploads/1621582705622-Boyne_Resorts_Logo.png</logo>
      <occupationalcategory>37-2012.00,Maids and Housekeeping Cleaners</occupationalcategory>
      <postalCode>49740</postalCode>
      <salary null="true" />
      <salaryEstimate null="true" />
      <sameas>https://boyneresorts.com/</sameas>
      <url>https://click.appcast.io/track/97qgops?cs=jsq&amp;exch=1a&amp;jg=3t1a&amp;bid=SSAKDDdbKVFCOLsOsUlBHA==</url>
   </job>
   <job>
      <company>Boyne Resorts</company>
      <jobdescription_opt><![CDATA[<b>Overview</b></br></br>Our Cashiers/Counter service team members play a key role in creating exceptional experiences for our guests in our food hall and counter style outlets. This entry level position will allow you to deliver fast service while being the last player in providing positive interactions with guests. This is a great opportunity to join our Food &amp; Beverage team while working for o ne of the world's leading vacation destinations in the world .</br></br>
<strong> Success Profile </strong> </br></br> Here are some of the top qualities that will help you be successful in this role: </br>
<ul>
 <li> Supportive </li>
 <li> Diligent </li>
 <li> Willing and Helpful </li>
 <li> Professional </li>
 <li> Disciplined </li>
 <li> Detailed </li>
</ul></br> 
<strong> SIGNING BONUS </strong> for Summer 2021 season. </br>
<ul>
 <li> $750 signing bonus 
  <ul>
   <li> $250 to be paid on first paycheck after 30 days of employment </li>
   <li> $500 at completion of contract </li>
  </ul></li>
</ul></br></br>
<b>Responsibilities</b></br></br>Picture yourself being a Cashier at Big Sky Resort and having the opportunity to:</br></br>*Provide amazing service for our guests while working the counter/check out area with a smile </br></br> *Demons trate excellent communication skills that allow you to deal with all guests in a positive manner </br></br> *Follow established procedures, systems and processes to perform all cashier duties including cash handling, guest check out, organizing and stocking items </br></br> *Maintain precision and attention to detail while completing transactions by the book </br></br> *Step into any support role and maintain harm onious relationships with other support team members by being open to completing any task or function that will support the service experience </br></br> *Demonstrate receptiveness to obtain an elevated knowledge of Big Sky Resort and the community, to share information with guests </br></br> *Showcase your cleanliness standards by maintaining the check out and surrounding area in i mpeccable order </br></br> *Learn and follow our Boyne Standards and Boyne Basics to better serve our guests</br></br>
<b>Qualifications</b></br></br>Recipe for Success </br></br> *Possess a passion for guest service and the hospitality industry </br></br> *Display a polite attitude to greet guests in a welcoming and professional manner </br></br> *Have a strong sense of urgency and responsibility for completing work quickly and correctly </br></br> * Possess the ability to e xcel in an environment with repetitive tasks in a steady or fast, even pace </br></br> *Exhibit clean work habits and ownership of a safe, clean work area </br></br> *Work within established standards and procedures </br></br> *Be available to work early, mid-day and evening shifts, weekends and holidays </br></br> *B e able to lift at least 25 pounds</br></br>How to stand out </br></br> *Submit a resume with your application </br></br> *Be ServSafe certified (Food Handler) </br></br> *Have proven prior experience or an enthusiastic willingness to learn</br></br>Additional information </br></br> Be a part of our full - time seasonal team and enjoy these great benefits! </br></br> *FREE Golf Pass with a refundable $150 +tax deposit for new employees and discounted passes for spouse and dependents </br></br> *Free Scenic Lift Pass for you, your spouse and dependents </br></br> *FREE Basecamp activities including zip line courses and discounted passes for spouse and dependents </br></br> *50% off Lodging rates for accommodation for friends and family (blackout dates apply) </br></br> *25% off Food discount at all outlets </br></br> *20%-30% off Retail discount at all outlets, gear and sponsor discounts </br></br> * Eligibility for affordable employee housing , a short walk or free bus ride away from work </br></br> *Qualify for 401k and Health benefits by meeting 1,000 and 1,500 hours respectively in an audit period]]></jobdescription_opt>
      <jobid>13819_9156-b1a3b468d756d75aaa2bde59076378ed</jobid>
      <jobtitle>Cashier/Counter Service - Signing Bonus Available</jobtitle>
      <jobtype>FULL_TIME</jobtype>
      <location>Manhattan,MT,United States</location>
      <logo>https://dev-jbk-ai.s3.amazonaws.com/company-logos/d-uploads/1621582705622-Boyne_Resorts_Logo.png</logo>
      <occupationalcategory />
      <postalCode>59741</postalCode>
      <salary null="true" />
      <salaryEstimate null="true" />
      <sameas>https://boyneresorts.com/</sameas>
      <url>https://click.appcast.io/track/9gg76e1?cs=jsq&amp;exch=1a&amp;jg=3stn&amp;bid=SSAKDDdbKVFCOLsOsUlBHA==</url>
   </job>
   <job>
      <company>Boyne Resorts</company>
      <jobdescription_opt><![CDATA[<b>Overview</b></br></br>As a 
<strong>Line Cook </strong>you are responsible for preparing food, helping the kitchen staff in preparation of food items, setting up assigned station in compliance with standards set by Chef. As a Boyne Mountain team member, there are so many awesome perks for you to take advantage of, such as: ski passes, golf passes, waterpark passes, and discounts for food, beverages, retail, daycare, and so much more! To learn more about Boyne Mountain Resort, employment perks, and employee testimonials, click here - Boyne Mountain Employment !</br></br>"Work Where You Love To Play!" at Boyne Mountain Resort.</br></br>
<b>Responsibilities</b></br></br>The 
<strong>Line Cook's </strong>typical job functions include: </br>
<ul>
 <li> Preparing food according to food handling guidelines and cooking procedures</li>
 <li> Measuring and mixing ingredients according to recipe or use record to prepare and prep food items</li>
 <li> Stocking and maintaining sufficient levels of food products at line stations to assure a smooth service period</li>
 <li> Communicating and coordinating production with other cooks, wait staff and members of the food and beverage team</li>
 <li> Possessing knowledge and/or become familiar with all kitchen equipment</li>
 <li> Adjusting thermostat controls to regulate temperature of ovens, broilers, grills, roasters, kettles, etc</li>
 <li> Observing and testing foods being cooked by tasting, smelling, and piercing with thermometer to determine proper preparation and cooking</li>
 <li> Plating and portioning food and maintain consistency according to presentation specifications, using records or specs</li>
 <li> Labeling, dating and rotating all stored food</li>
 <li> Performing closing procedures including equipment maintenance and shut off, cleaning, sanitation, and organization of kitchen, walk-in coolers, and all storage areas</li>
</ul></br></br>
<b>Qualifications</b></br></br>This position may for you if: </br>
<ul>
 <li> You are 18 years old </li>
 <li> You have achieved a high school diploma or general education degree (GED) </li>
 <li> You have previous kitchen experience </li>
 <li> You are available to work days, evenings, weekends and holidays </li>
</ul>]]></jobdescription_opt>
      <jobid>13819_9519-6bcaed2becdae28c8ee08b64fdd4e008</jobid>
      <jobtitle>Line Cook | Everett's</jobtitle>
      <jobtype>FULL_TIME</jobtype>
      <location>Walloon Lake,MI,United States</location>
      <logo>https://dev-jbk-ai.s3.amazonaws.com/company-logos/d-uploads/1621582705622-Boyne_Resorts_Logo.png</logo>
      <occupationalcategory>35-2014.00,Cooks, Restaurant</occupationalcategory>
      <postalCode>49796</postalCode>
      <salary null="true" />
      <salaryEstimate null="true" />
      <sameas>https://boyneresorts.com/</sameas>
      <url>https://click.appcast.io/track/9gg4v69?cs=jsq&amp;exch=1a&amp;jg=3t1b&amp;bid=SSAKDDdbKVFCOLsOsUlBHA==</url>
   </job>
   <job>
      <company>Boyne Resorts</company>
      <jobdescription_opt><![CDATA[<b>Overview</b></br></br>As a 
<strong>Line Cook </strong>you are responsible for preparing food, helping the kitchen staff in preparation of food items, setting up assigned station in compliance with standards set by Chef. As a Boyne Mountain team member, there are so many awesome perks for you to take advantage of, such as: ski passes, golf passes, waterpark passes, and discounts for food, beverages, retail, daycare, and so much more! To learn more about Boyne Mountain Resort, employment perks, and employee testimonials, click here - Boyne Mountain Employment !</br></br>"Work Where You Love To Play!" at Boyne Mountain Resort.</br></br>
<b>Responsibilities</b></br></br>The 
<strong>Line Cook's </strong>typical job functions include: </br>
<ul>
 <li> Preparing food according to food handling guidelines and cooking procedures</li>
 <li> Measuring and mixing ingredients according to recipe or use record to prepare and prep food items</li>
 <li> Stocking and maintaining sufficient levels of food products at line stations to assure a smooth service period</li>
 <li> Communicating and coordinating production with other cooks, wait staff and members of the food and beverage team</li>
 <li> Possessing knowledge and/or become familiar with all kitchen equipment</li>
 <li> Adjusting thermostat controls to regulate temperature of ovens, broilers, grills, roasters, kettles, etc</li>
 <li> Observing and testing foods being cooked by tasting, smelling, and piercing with thermometer to determine proper preparation and cooking</li>
 <li> Plating and portioning food and maintain consistency according to presentation specifications, using records or specs</li>
 <li> Labeling, dating and rotating all stored food</li>
 <li> Performing closing procedures including equipment maintenance and shut off, cleaning, sanitation, and organization of kitchen, walk-in coolers, and all storage areas</li>
</ul></br></br>
<b>Qualifications</b></br></br>This position may for you if: </br>
<ul>
 <li> You are 18 years old </li>
 <li> You have achieved a high school diploma or general education degree (GED) </li>
 <li> You have previous kitchen experience </li>
 <li> You are available to work days, evenings, weekends and holidays </li>
</ul>]]></jobdescription_opt>
      <jobid>13819_9519-feec894eda86602d2310ef53cc8e8f38</jobid>
      <jobtitle>Line Cook | Everett's</jobtitle>
      <jobtype>FULL_TIME</jobtype>
      <location>Brutus,MI,United States</location>
      <logo>https://dev-jbk-ai.s3.amazonaws.com/company-logos/d-uploads/1621582705622-Boyne_Resorts_Logo.png</logo>
      <occupationalcategory>35-2014.00,Cooks, Restaurant</occupationalcategory>
      <postalCode>49716</postalCode>
      <salary null="true" />
      <salaryEstimate null="true" />
      <sameas>https://boyneresorts.com/</sameas>
      <url>https://click.appcast.io/track/9gg4v62?cs=jsq&amp;exch=1a&amp;jg=3t1b&amp;bid=SSAKDDdbKVFCOLsOsUlBHA==</url>
   </job>
   <job>
      <company>Boyne Resorts</company>
      <jobdescription_opt><![CDATA[<b>Overview</b></br></br>As a 
<strong>Dishwasher </strong>you are responsible for keeping dish area, restaurant equipment and utensils in clean and orderly condition. As a Boyne Mountain team member, there are so many awesome perks for you to take advantage of, such as: ski passes, golf passes, waterpark passes, and discounts for food, beverages, retail, daycare, and so much more! To learn more about Boyne Mountain Resort, employment perks, and employee testimonials, click here - Boyne Mountain Employment !</br></br>"Work Where You Love To Play!" at Boyne Mountain Resort.</br></br>
<b>Responsibilities</b></br></br>The
<strong> Dishwasher's </strong>typical job functions include: </br>
<ul>
 <li> Rinsing, scrubbing and scraping food from all dirty dishes, silverware, and cookware and washing them by hand or place them in racks or on conveyor to dish washing machine</li>
 <li> Placing all clean dishes in proper storage areas</li>
 <li> Cleaning and maintaining work areas, equipment and utensils</li>
 <li> Removing garbage and place refuse in designated pickup area</li>
 <li> Cleaning drains, disposals and sinks to ensure proper drainage</li>
 <li> Following all health regulations and assisting in maintaining a sanitary environment</li>
 <li> Setting up dish machine and ensuring machine is operating properly</li>
 <li> Sweeping and moping kitchen floors</li>
 <li> Washing worktables, walls, refrigerators and other kitchen surfaces</li>
</ul></br></br>
<b>Qualifications</b></br></br>This position may be for you if: </br>
<ul>
 <li> You are at least 16 years old </li>
 <li> You are available to work days, evenings, weekends and holidays </li>
 <li> You are able to lift up to 25 pounds </li>
 <li> You are able to stand for long periods of time </li>
</ul>]]></jobdescription_opt>
      <jobid>13819_9518-1afa411082397b5a2e499c33fbc4bd3b</jobid>
      <jobtitle>Dishwasher | Everett's</jobtitle>
      <jobtype>FULL_TIME</jobtype>
      <location>Boyne City,MI,United States</location>
      <logo>https://dev-jbk-ai.s3.amazonaws.com/company-logos/d-uploads/1621582705622-Boyne_Resorts_Logo.png</logo>
      <occupationalcategory>35-9021.00,Dishwashers</occupationalcategory>
      <postalCode>49712</postalCode>
      <salary null="true" />
      <salaryEstimate null="true" />
      <sameas>https://boyneresorts.com/</sameas>
      <url>https://click.appcast.io/track/9gg4v75?cs=jsq&amp;exch=1a&amp;jg=3t1b&amp;bid=SSAKDDdbKVFCOLsOsUlBHA==</url>
   </job>
   <job>
      <company>Boyne Resorts</company>
      <jobdescription_opt><![CDATA[<b>Overview</b></br></br>As a 
<strong>Dishwasher </strong>you are responsible for keeping dish area, restaurant equipment and utensils in clean and orderly condition. As a Boyne Mountain team member, there are so many awesome perks for you to take advantage of, such as: ski passes, golf passes, waterpark passes, and discounts for food, beverages, retail, daycare, and so much more! To learn more about Boyne Mountain Resort, employment perks, and employee testimonials, click here - Boyne Mountain Employment !</br></br>"Work Where You Love To Play!" at Boyne Mountain Resort.</br></br>
<b>Responsibilities</b></br></br>The 
<strong>Dishwasher's </strong>typical job functions include: </br>
<ul>
 <li> Rinsing, scrubbing and scraping food from all dirty dishes, silverware, and cookware and washing them by hand or place them in racks or on conveyor to dishwashing machine</li>
 <li> Placing all clean dishes in proper storage areas</li>
 <li> Cleaning and maintaining work areas, equipment and utensils</li>
 <li> Removing garbage and place refuse in designated pickup area</li>
 <li> Cleaning drains, disposals and sinks to ensure proper drainage</li>
 <li> Following all health regulations and assisting in maintaining a sanitary environment</li>
 <li> Setting up dish machine and ensuring machine is operating properly</li>
 <li> Sweeping and moping kitchen floors</li>
 <li> Washing worktables, walls, refrigerators and other kitchen surfaces</li>
</ul></br></br>
<b>Qualifications</b></br></br>This position may be for you if: </br>
<ul>
 <li> You are at least 16 years old </li>
 <li> You are available to work days, evenings, weekends and holidays </li>
 <li> You are able to lift up to 25 pounds </li>
 <li> You are able to stand for long periods of time </li>
</ul>]]></jobdescription_opt>
      <jobid>13819_9544-fa87d30a365229aad20c521c483558d8</jobid>
      <jobtitle>Banquet Dishwasher</jobtitle>
      <jobtype>FULL_TIME</jobtype>
      <location>Alanson,MI,United States</location>
      <logo>https://dev-jbk-ai.s3.amazonaws.com/company-logos/d-uploads/1621582705622-Boyne_Resorts_Logo.png</logo>
      <occupationalcategory>35-9021.00,Dishwashers</occupationalcategory>
      <postalCode>49706</postalCode>
      <salary null="true" />
      <salaryEstimate null="true" />
      <sameas>https://boyneresorts.com/</sameas>
      <url>https://click.appcast.io/track/9gg4v4k?cs=jsq&amp;exch=1a&amp;jg=3t1b&amp;bid=SSAKDDdbKVFCOLsOsUlBHA==</url>
   </job>
   <job>
      <company>Boyne Resorts</company>
      <jobdescription_opt><![CDATA[<b>Overview</b></br></br>Inn at Bay Harbor is a Marriott Autograph Collection Hotel nestled on the shoreline of Lake Michigan. It is a place and experience that is Exactly Like Nothing Else . </br></br> The Housekeeping Room Attendant is a part or full time year round position. The primary focus of this position is to ensure clean, orderly,and attractive rooms in hotel, resort cottages, and surrounding common areas. Candidate should be able to perform all position duties in an efficient manner according to the standards established by the Inn at Bay Harbor. </br></br> The starting wage for this position is $14/hour. </br></br> A $200 bonus is available for new hires to this department! $100 will be paid after 45 days, and an additional $100 after 90 days.</br></br>
<strong> END OF SEASON BONUS AVAILABLE! </strong>Housekeeping Team Members who work our full season, from June 15 th through October 31 st , and maintain their scheduled shifts, will be eligible for a $1 per hour bonus for each hour they worked between those dates.</br></br>
<b>Responsibilities</b></br></br>
<ul>
 <li> Obtain list of vacant rooms which need to be cleaned immediately and list of prospective check outs in order to prepare work assignments. </li>
 <li> Examine rooms, halls, and lobbies, and report any maintenance concerns to supervisor. </li>
 <li> Change and replenish linens and amenities in room, distribute soiled articles and linens. </li>
 <li> Replace and/or clean soiled items in room. </li>
 <li> Disinfect and sterilize kitchenette and bathroom areas. </li>
 <li> Sweep, vacuum and polish floor areas. </li>
 <li> Clean rugs, carpets, upholstered furniture, and draperies. </li>
 <li> Dust furniture and equipment. </li>
 <li> Wash walls, ceiling, woodwork, windows, door panels, and sills. </li>
 <li> Empty wastebaskets and replaces liners. </li>
 <li> Clean all outdoor patio areas and furniture. </li>
 <li> Ensure cleaning checklist for every room is complete and inspect work to meet standards of cleanliness. </li>
 <li> Take inventory to ensure adequate supplies. Restock carts and storage closets. </li>
 <li> Keep utility and storage rooms in clean and orderly condition. </li>
 <li> Complete any special tasks assigned by management. </li>
 <li> Respond to Guest requests for additional supplies or information. </li>
 <li> Keep supervisor promptly and fully informed of all problems or unusual matters of significance. </li>
 <li> Maintain a clean, well-organized work area. </li>
 <li> Assist other room attendants when necessary in any area of the resort. </li>
 <li> Complete section report in allotted time frame and update status according to what has been cleaned. </li>
</ul></br></br>
<b>Qualifications</b></br></br>Occasional heavy lifting, up to and including 25 lbs</br></br>Applicants must be at least 18 years old </br></br> Weekends and holidays are our peak times </br></br> Occasional long periods of standing </br></br> Team player attitude expected </br></br> Our department provides flexible scheduling and for those hired into full-time year round positions, you are provided with medical, dental and vision options.</br></br>Inn at Bay Harbor Team Members and their eligible family members are provided with a benefit package like no other. Working here gives you access to both Boyne Resorts and Marriott team discounts. Simply put, you get the best of both worlds.]]></jobdescription_opt>
      <jobid>13819_9670-fa87d30a365229aad20c521c483558d8</jobid>
      <jobtitle>Housekeeping Room Attendant</jobtitle>
      <jobtype>FULL_TIME</jobtype>
      <location>Alanson,MI,United States</location>
      <logo>https://dev-jbk-ai.s3.amazonaws.com/company-logos/d-uploads/1621582705622-Boyne_Resorts_Logo.png</logo>
      <occupationalcategory>37-2012.00,Maids and Housekeeping Cleaners</occupationalcategory>
      <postalCode>49706</postalCode>
      <salary null="true" />
      <salaryEstimate null="true" />
      <sameas>https://boyneresorts.com/</sameas>
      <url>https://click.appcast.io/track/9gg4v57?cs=jsq&amp;exch=1a&amp;jg=3t1b&amp;bid=SSAKDDdbKVFCOLsOsUlBHA==</url>
   </job>
   <job>
      <company>Boyne Resorts</company>
      <jobdescription_opt><![CDATA[<b>Overview</b></br></br>As a 
<strong>Line Cook </strong>you are responsible for preparing food, helping the kitchen staff in preparation of food items, setting up assigned station in compliance with standards set by Chef. As a Boyne Mountain team member, there are so many awesome perks for you to take advantage of, such as: ski passes, golf passes, waterpark passes, and discounts for food, beverages, retail, daycare, and so much more! To learn more about Boyne Mountain Resort, employment perks, and employee testimonials, click here - Boyne Mountain Employment !</br></br>"Work Where You Love To Play!" at Boyne Mountain Resort.</br></br>
<b>Responsibilities</b></br></br>The 
<strong>Line Cook's </strong>typical job functions include: </br>
<ul>
 <li> Preparing food according to food handling guidelines and cooking procedures</li>
 <li> Measuring and mixing ingredients according to recipe or use record to prepare and prep food items</li>
 <li> Stocking and maintaining sufficient levels of food products at line stations to assure a smooth service period</li>
 <li> Communicating and coordinating production with other cooks, wait staff and members of the food and beverage team</li>
 <li> Possessing knowledge and/or become familiar with all kitchen equipment</li>
 <li> Adjusting thermostat controls to regulate temperature of ovens, broilers, grills, roasters, kettles, etc</li>
 <li> Observing and testing foods being cooked by tasting, smelling, and piercing with thermometer to determine proper preparation and cooking</li>
 <li> Plating and portioning food and maintain consistency according to presentation specifications, using records or specs</li>
 <li> Labeling, dating and rotating all stored food</li>
 <li> Performing closing procedures including equipment maintenance and shut off, cleaning, sanitation, and organization of kitchen, walk-in coolers, and all storage areas</li>
</ul></br></br>
<b>Qualifications</b></br></br>This position may for you if: </br>
<ul>
 <li> You are 18 years old </li>
 <li> You have achieved a high school diploma or general education degree (GED) </li>
 <li> You have previous kitchen experience </li>
 <li> You are available to work days, evenings, weekends and holidays </li>
</ul>]]></jobdescription_opt>
      <jobid>13819_9519-ba97b6a7f9cc40249bcc4088ed19286f</jobid>
      <jobtitle>Line Cook | Everett's</jobtitle>
      <jobtype>FULL_TIME</jobtype>
      <location>Eastport,MI,United States</location>
      <logo>https://dev-jbk-ai.s3.amazonaws.com/company-logos/d-uploads/1621582705622-Boyne_Resorts_Logo.png</logo>
      <occupationalcategory>35-2014.00,Cooks, Restaurant</occupationalcategory>
      <postalCode>49627</postalCode>
      <salary null="true" />
      <salaryEstimate null="true" />
      <sameas>https://boyneresorts.com/</sameas>
      <url>https://click.appcast.io/track/9gg4v4q?cs=jsq&amp;exch=1a&amp;jg=3t1b&amp;bid=SSAKDDdbKVFCOLsOsUlBHA==</url>
   </job>
   <job>
      <company>Boyne Resorts</company>
      <jobdescription_opt><![CDATA[<b>Overview</b></br></br>As a 
<strong>Line Cook </strong>you are responsible for preparing food, helping the kitchen staff in preparation of food items, setting up assigned station in compliance with standards set by Chef. A s a Boyne Mountain team member, there are so many awesome perks for you to take advantage of, such as: ski passes, golf passes, waterpark passes, and discounts for food, beverages, retail, daycare, and so much more! To learn more about Boyne Mountain Resort, employment perks, and employee testimonials, click here - Boyne Mountain Employment !</br></br>"Work Where You Love To Play!" at Boyne Mountain Resort.</br></br>
<b>Responsibilities</b></br></br>The 
<strong>Line Cook's </strong>typical job functions include: </br>
<ul>
 <li> Preparing food according to food handling guidelines and cooking procedures</li>
 <li> Measuring and mixing ingredients according to recipe or use record to prepare and prep food items</li>
 <li> Stocking and maintaining sufficient levels of food products at line stations to assure a smooth service period</li>
 <li> Communicating and coordinating production with other cooks, wait staff and members of the food and beverage team</li>
 <li> Possessing knowledge and/or become familiar with all kitchen equipment</li>
 <li> Adjusting thermostat controls to regulate temperature of ovens, broilers, grills, roasters, kettles, etc</li>
 <li> Observing and testing foods being cooked by tasting, smelling, and piercing with thermometer to determine proper preparation and cooking</li>
 <li> Plating and portioning food and maintain consistency according to presentation specifications, using records or specs</li>
 <li> Labeling, dating and rotating all stored food</li>
 <li> Performing closing procedures including equipment maintenance and shut off, cleaning, sanitation, and organization of kitchen, walk-in coolers, and all storage areas</li>
</ul></br></br>
<b>Qualifications</b></br></br>This position may for you if: </br>
<ul>
 <li> You are 18 years old </li>
 <li> You have achieved a high school diploma or general education degree (GED) </li>
 <li> You have previous kitchen experience </li>
 <li> You are available to work days, evenings, weekends and holidays </li>
</ul>]]></jobdescription_opt>
      <jobid>13819_9541-63db3ba2386ef041eaa95ed2b8836f80</jobid>
      <jobtitle>Line Cook | Beach House</jobtitle>
      <jobtype>FULL_TIME</jobtype>
      <location>Harbor Springs,MI,United States</location>
      <logo>https://dev-jbk-ai.s3.amazonaws.com/company-logos/d-uploads/1621582705622-Boyne_Resorts_Logo.png</logo>
      <occupationalcategory>35-2014.00,Cooks, Restaurant</occupationalcategory>
      <postalCode>49740</postalCode>
      <salary null="true" />
      <salaryEstimate null="true" />
      <sameas>https://boyneresorts.com/</sameas>
      <url>https://click.appcast.io/track/9gg4v92?cs=jsq&amp;exch=1a&amp;jg=3t1b&amp;bid=SSAKDDdbKVFCOLsOsUlBHA==</url>
   </job>
   <job>
      <company>Boyne Resorts</company>
      <jobdescription_opt><![CDATA[<b>Overview</b></br></br>As a 
<strong>Housekeeping Room Attendant</strong>, you are responsible for ensuring clean, orderly, and attractive rooms in our resort's hotels and condos. In this particular position, the 
<strong>average room attendant makes $15 per hour</strong>... but you can make as much as you want, depending on how many rooms you clean. The power is in your hands! There are also lots of 
<strong>overtime opportunities</strong> for this position, along with 
<strong>affordable onsite daycare</strong>! </br></br> As a Boyne Mountain team member, there are so many awesome perks for you to take advantage of, such as: ski passes, golf passes, waterpark passes, and discounts for food, beverages, retail, daycare, and so much more! To learn more about Boyne Mountain Resort, employment perks, and employee testimonials, click here - Boyne Mountain Employment !</br></br>"Work Where You Love To Play!" at Boyne Mountain Resort.</br></br>
<b>Responsibilities</b></br></br>The 
<strong>Housekeeping Room Attendant</strong>
<strong>'s</strong> typical job functions include: </br>
<ul>
 <li> Clean guest rooms to established resort standards to ensure guest satisfaction and prompt check-in times </li>
 <li> Examine rooms, halls, and lobbies, and report any maintenance concerns to supervisor </li>
 <li> Ensure cleaning checklist for every room is complete and inspect work to meet standards of cleanliness </li>
 <li> Take inventory to ensure adequate supplies. Restock carts and storage closets </li>
 <li> Keep utility and storage rooms in clean and orderly condition </li>
 <li> Respond to guest requests for additional supplies or information </li>
 <li> Keep supervisor promptly and fully informed of all problems or unusual matters of significance </li>
 <li> Assist other room attendants when necessary in any area of the resort </li>
 <li> Complete section reports and other required paperwork in a timely manner </li>
</ul></br></br>
<b>Qualifications</b></br></br>This position might be for you if: </br>
<ul>
 <li> You are at least 18 years old </li>
 <li> You are available to work evenings, weekends and holidays </li>
 <li> Achieved a high school diploma or general education degree (GED) </li>
</ul>]]></jobdescription_opt>
      <jobid>13819_9649-1afa411082397b5a2e499c33fbc4bd3b</jobid>
      <jobtitle>Housekeeping Room Attendant</jobtitle>
      <jobtype>FULL_TIME</jobtype>
      <location>Boyne City,MI,United States</location>
      <logo>https://dev-jbk-ai.s3.amazonaws.com/company-logos/d-uploads/1621582705622-Boyne_Resorts_Logo.png</logo>
      <occupationalcategory>37-2012.00,Maids and Housekeeping Cleaners</occupationalcategory>
      <postalCode>49712</postalCode>
      <salary null="true" />
      <salaryEstimate null="true" />
      <sameas>https://boyneresorts.com/</sameas>
      <url>https://click.appcast.io/track/9gg4v7t?cs=jsq&amp;exch=1a&amp;jg=3t1b&amp;bid=SSAKDDdbKVFCOLsOsUlBHA==</url>
   </job>
   <job>
      <company>Boyne Resorts</company>
      <jobdescription_opt><![CDATA[<b>Overview</b></br></br>As a 
<strong>Housekeeping Room Attendant</strong>, you are responsible for ensuring clean, orderly, and attractive rooms in our resort's hotels and condos. In this particular position, the 
<strong>average room attendant makes $15 per hour</strong>... but you can make as much as you want, depending on how many rooms you clean. The power is in your hands! There are also lots of 
<strong>overtime opportunities</strong> for this position, along with 
<strong>affordable onsite daycare</strong>! </br></br> As a Boyne Mountain team member, there are so many awesome perks for you to take advantage of, such as: ski passes, golf passes, waterpark passes, and discounts for food, beverages, retail, daycare, and so much more! To learn more about Boyne Mountain Resort, employment perks, and employee testimonials, click here - Boyne Mountain Employment !</br></br>"Work Where You Love To Play!" at Boyne Mountain Resort.</br></br>
<b>Responsibilities</b></br></br>The 
<strong>Housekeeping Room Attendant</strong>
<strong>'s</strong> typical job functions include: </br>
<ul>
 <li> Clean guest rooms to established resort standards to ensure guest satisfaction and prompt check-in times </li>
 <li> Examine rooms, halls, and lobbies, and report any maintenance concerns to supervisor </li>
 <li> Ensure cleaning checklist for every room is complete and inspect work to meet standards of cleanliness </li>
 <li> Take inventory to ensure adequate supplies. Restock carts and storage closets </li>
 <li> Keep utility and storage rooms in clean and orderly condition </li>
 <li> Respond to guest requests for additional supplies or information </li>
 <li> Keep supervisor promptly and fully informed of all problems or unusual matters of significance </li>
 <li> Assist other room attendants when necessary in any area of the resort </li>
 <li> Complete section reports and other required paperwork in a timely manner </li>
</ul></br></br>
<b>Qualifications</b></br></br>This position might be for you if: </br>
<ul>
 <li> You are at least 18 years old </li>
 <li> You are available to work evenings, weekends and holidays </li>
 <li> Achieved a high school diploma or general education degree (GED) </li>
</ul>]]></jobdescription_opt>
      <jobid>13819_9649</jobid>
      <jobtitle>Housekeeping Room Attendant</jobtitle>
      <jobtype>FULL_TIME</jobtype>
      <location>Boyne Falls,MI,United States</location>
      <logo>https://dev-jbk-ai.s3.amazonaws.com/company-logos/d-uploads/1621582705622-Boyne_Resorts_Logo.png</logo>
      <occupationalcategory>37-2012.00,Maids and Housekeeping Cleaners</occupationalcategory>
      <postalCode>49713</postalCode>
      <salary null="true" />
      <salaryEstimate null="true" />
      <sameas>https://boyneresorts.com/</sameas>
      <url>https://click.appcast.io/track/92v1bb1?cs=jsq&amp;exch=1a&amp;jg=3t1b&amp;bid=SSAKDDdbKVFCOLsOsUlBHA==</url>
   </job>
   <job>
      <company>Boyne Resorts</company>
      <jobdescription_opt><![CDATA[<b>Overview</b></br></br>As a 
<strong>Housekeeping Room Attendant</strong>, you are responsible for ensuring clean, orderly, and attractive rooms in our resort's hotels and condos. In this particular position, the 
<strong>average room attendant makes $15 per hour</strong>... but you can make as much as you want, depending on how many rooms you clean. The power is in your hands! There are also lots of 
<strong>overtime opportunities</strong> for this position, along with 
<strong>affordable onsite daycare</strong>! </br></br> As a Boyne Mountain team member, there are so many awesome perks for you to take advantage of, such as: ski passes, golf passes, waterpark passes, and discounts for food, beverages, retail, daycare, and so much more! To learn more about Boyne Mountain Resort, employment perks, and employee testimonials, click here - Boyne Mountain Employment !</br></br>"Work Where You Love To Play!" at Boyne Mountain Resort.</br></br>
<b>Responsibilities</b></br></br>The 
<strong>Housekeeping Room Attendant</strong>
<strong>'s</strong> typical job functions include: </br>
<ul>
 <li> Clean guest rooms to established resort standards to ensure guest satisfaction and prompt check-in times </li>
 <li> Examine rooms, halls, and lobbies, and report any maintenance concerns to supervisor </li>
 <li> Ensure cleaning checklist for every room is complete and inspect work to meet standards of cleanliness </li>
 <li> Take inventory to ensure adequate supplies. Restock carts and storage closets </li>
 <li> Keep utility and storage rooms in clean and orderly condition </li>
 <li> Respond to guest requests for additional supplies or information </li>
 <li> Keep supervisor promptly and fully informed of all problems or unusual matters of significance </li>
 <li> Assist other room attendants when necessary in any area of the resort </li>
 <li> Complete section reports and other required paperwork in a timely manner </li>
</ul></br></br>
<b>Qualifications</b></br></br>This position might be for you if: </br>
<ul>
 <li> You are at least 18 years old </li>
 <li> You are available to work evenings, weekends and holidays </li>
 <li> Achieved a high school diploma or general education degree (GED) </li>
</ul>]]></jobdescription_opt>
      <jobid>13819_9649-63db3ba2386ef041eaa95ed2b8836f80</jobid>
      <jobtitle>Housekeeping Room Attendant</jobtitle>
      <jobtype>FULL_TIME</jobtype>
      <location>Harbor Springs,MI,United States</location>
      <logo>https://dev-jbk-ai.s3.amazonaws.com/company-logos/d-uploads/1621582705622-Boyne_Resorts_Logo.png</logo>
      <occupationalcategory>37-2012.00,Maids and Housekeeping Cleaners</occupationalcategory>
      <postalCode>49740</postalCode>
      <salary null="true" />
      <salaryEstimate null="true" />
      <sameas>https://boyneresorts.com/</sameas>
      <url>https://click.appcast.io/track/9gg4v4a?cs=jsq&amp;exch=1a&amp;jg=3t1b&amp;bid=SSAKDDdbKVFCOLsOsUlBHA==</url>
   </job>
   <job>
      <company>Boyne Resorts</company>
      <jobdescription_opt><![CDATA[<b>Overview</b></br></br>As a 
<strong>Dishwasher </strong>you are responsible for keeping dish area, restaurant equipment and utensils in clean and orderly condition. As a Boyne Mountain team member, there are so many awesome perks for you to take advantage of, such as: ski passes, golf passes, waterpark passes, and discounts for food, beverages, retail, daycare, and so much more! To learn more about Boyne Mountain Resort, employment perks, and employee testimonials, click here - Boyne Mountain Employment !</br></br>"Work Where You Love To Play!" at Boyne Mountain Resort.</br></br>
<b>Responsibilities</b></br></br>The 
<strong>Dishwasher's </strong>typical job functions include: </br>
<ul>
 <li> Rinsing, scrubbing and scraping food from all dirty dishes, silverware, and cookware and washing them by hand or place them in racks or on conveyor to dishwashing machine</li>
 <li> Placing all clean dishes in proper storage areas</li>
 <li> Cleaning and maintaining work areas, equipment and utensils</li>
 <li> Removing garbage and place refuse in designated pickup area</li>
 <li> Cleaning drains, disposals and sinks to ensure proper drainage</li>
 <li> Following all health regulations and assisting in maintaining a sanitary environment</li>
 <li> Setting up dish machine and ensuring machine is operating properly</li>
 <li> Sweeping and moping kitchen floors</li>
 <li> Washing worktables, walls, refrigerators and other kitchen surfaces</li>
</ul></br></br>
<b>Qualifications</b></br></br>This position may be for you if: </br>
<ul>
 <li> You are at least 16 years old </li>
 <li> You are available to work days, evenings, weekends and holidays </li>
 <li> You are able to lift up to 25 pounds </li>
 <li> You are able to stand for long periods of time </li>
</ul>]]></jobdescription_opt>
      <jobid>13819_9540-aa569cae1e44fa56091a82ef9ecea0e9</jobid>
      <jobtitle>Dishwasher | Beach House</jobtitle>
      <jobtype>FULL_TIME</jobtype>
      <location>Bay Shore,MI,United States</location>
      <logo>https://dev-jbk-ai.s3.amazonaws.com/company-logos/d-uploads/1621582705622-Boyne_Resorts_Logo.png</logo>
      <occupationalcategory />
      <postalCode>49711</postalCode>
      <salary null="true" />
      <salaryEstimate null="true" />
      <sameas>https://boyneresorts.com/</sameas>
      <url>https://click.appcast.io/track/9gg4v7p?cs=jsq&amp;exch=1a&amp;jg=3t1b&amp;bid=SSAKDDdbKVFCOLsOsUlBHA==</url>
   </job>
   <job>
      <company>Boyne Resorts</company>
      <jobdescription_opt><![CDATA[<b>Overview</b></br></br>As a 
<strong>Dishwasher </strong>you are responsible for keeping dish area, restaurant equipment and utensils in clean and orderly condition. As a Boyne Mountain team member, there are so many awesome perks for you to take advantage of, such as: ski passes, golf passes, waterpark passes, and discounts for food, beverages, retail, daycare, and so much more! To learn more about Boyne Mountain Resort, employment perks, and employee testimonials, click here - Boyne Mountain Employment !</br></br>"Work Where You Love To Play!" at Boyne Mountain Resort.</br></br>
<b>Responsibilities</b></br></br>The
<strong> Dishwasher's </strong>typical job functions include: </br>
<ul>
 <li> Rinsing, scrubbing and scraping food from all dirty dishes, silverware, and cookware and washing them by hand or place them in racks or on conveyor to dish washing machine</li>
 <li> Placing all clean dishes in proper storage areas</li>
 <li> Cleaning and maintaining work areas, equipment and utensils</li>
 <li> Removing garbage and place refuse in designated pickup area</li>
 <li> Cleaning drains, disposals and sinks to ensure proper drainage</li>
 <li> Following all health regulations and assisting in maintaining a sanitary environment</li>
 <li> Setting up dish machine and ensuring machine is operating properly</li>
 <li> Sweeping and moping kitchen floors</li>
 <li> Washing worktables, walls, refrigerators and other kitchen surfaces</li>
</ul></br></br>
<b>Qualifications</b></br></br>This position may be for you if: </br>
<ul>
 <li> You are at least 16 years old </li>
 <li> You are available to work days, evenings, weekends and holidays </li>
 <li> You are able to lift up to 25 pounds </li>
 <li> You are able to stand for long periods of time </li>
</ul>]]></jobdescription_opt>
      <jobid>13819_9518-63db3ba2386ef041eaa95ed2b8836f80</jobid>
      <jobtitle>Dishwasher | Everett's</jobtitle>
      <jobtype>FULL_TIME</jobtype>
      <location>Harbor Springs,MI,United States</location>
      <logo>https://dev-jbk-ai.s3.amazonaws.com/company-logos/d-uploads/1621582705622-Boyne_Resorts_Logo.png</logo>
      <occupationalcategory>35-9021.00,Dishwashers</occupationalcategory>
      <postalCode>49740</postalCode>
      <salary null="true" />
      <salaryEstimate null="true" />
      <sameas>https://boyneresorts.com/</sameas>
      <url>https://click.appcast.io/track/9gg4v3w?cs=jsq&amp;exch=1a&amp;jg=3t1b&amp;bid=SSAKDDdbKVFCOLsOsUlBHA==</url>
   </job>
   <job>
      <company>Boyne Resorts</company>
      <jobdescription_opt><![CDATA[<b>Overview</b></br></br>As a 
<strong>Line Cook </strong>you are responsible for preparing food, helping the kitchen staff in preparation of food items, setting up assigned station in compliance with standards set by Chef. A s a Boyne Mountain team member, there are so many awesome perks for you to take advantage of, such as: ski passes, golf passes, waterpark passes, and discounts for food, beverages, retail, daycare, and so much more! To learn more about Boyne Mountain Resort, employment perks, and employee testimonials, click here - Boyne Mountain Employment !</br></br>"Work Where You Love To Play!" at Boyne Mountain Resort.</br></br>
<b>Responsibilities</b></br></br>The 
<strong>Line Cook's </strong>typical job functions include: </br>
<ul>
 <li> Preparing food according to food handling guidelines and cooking procedures</li>
 <li> Measuring and mixing ingredients according to recipe or use record to prepare and prep food items</li>
 <li> Stocking and maintaining sufficient levels of food products at line stations to assure a smooth service period</li>
 <li> Communicating and coordinating production with other cooks, wait staff and members of the food and beverage team</li>
 <li> Possessing knowledge and/or become familiar with all kitchen equipment</li>
 <li> Adjusting thermostat controls to regulate temperature of ovens, broilers, grills, roasters, kettles, etc</li>
 <li> Observing and testing foods being cooked by tasting, smelling, and piercing with thermometer to determine proper preparation and cooking</li>
 <li> Plating and portioning food and maintain consistency according to presentation specifications, using records or specs</li>
 <li> Labeling, dating and rotating all stored food</li>
 <li> Performing closing procedures including equipment maintenance and shut off, cleaning, sanitation, and organization of kitchen, walk-in coolers, and all storage areas</li>
</ul></br></br>
<b>Qualifications</b></br></br>This position may for you if: </br>
<ul>
 <li> You are 18 years old </li>
 <li> You have achieved a high school diploma or general education degree (GED) </li>
 <li> You have previous kitchen experience </li>
 <li> You are available to work days, evenings, weekends and holidays </li>
</ul>]]></jobdescription_opt>
      <jobid>13819_9541-aa569cae1e44fa56091a82ef9ecea0e9</jobid>
      <jobtitle>Line Cook | Beach House</jobtitle>
      <jobtype>FULL_TIME</jobtype>
      <location>Bay Shore,MI,United States</location>
      <logo>https://dev-jbk-ai.s3.amazonaws.com/company-logos/d-uploads/1621582705622-Boyne_Resorts_Logo.png</logo>
      <occupationalcategory>35-2014.00,Cooks, Restaurant</occupationalcategory>
      <postalCode>49711</postalCode>
      <salary null="true" />
      <salaryEstimate null="true" />
      <sameas>https://boyneresorts.com/</sameas>
      <url>https://click.appcast.io/track/9gg4va4?cs=jsq&amp;exch=1a&amp;jg=3t1b&amp;bid=SSAKDDdbKVFCOLsOsUlBHA==</url>
   </job>
   <job>
      <company>Boyne Resorts</company>
      <jobdescription_opt><![CDATA[<b>Overview</b></br></br>As a 
<strong>Line Cook </strong>you are responsible for preparing food, helping the kitchen staff in preparation of food items, setting up assigned station in compliance with standards set by Chef. A s a Boyne Mountain team member, there are so many awesome perks for you to take advantage of, such as: ski passes, golf passes, waterpark passes, and discounts for food, beverages, retail, daycare, and so much more! To learn more about Boyne Mountain Resort, employment perks, and employee testimonials, click here - Boyne Mountain Employment !</br></br>"Work Where You Love To Play!" at Boyne Mountain Resort.</br></br>
<b>Responsibilities</b></br></br>The 
<strong>Line Cook's </strong>typical job functions include: </br>
<ul>
 <li> Preparing food according to food handling guidelines and cooking procedures</li>
 <li> Measuring and mixing ingredients according to recipe or use record to prepare and prep food items</li>
 <li> Stocking and maintaining sufficient levels of food products at line stations to assure a smooth service period</li>
 <li> Communicating and coordinating production with other cooks, wait staff and members of the food and beverage team</li>
 <li> Possessing knowledge and/or become familiar with all kitchen equipment</li>
 <li> Adjusting thermostat controls to regulate temperature of ovens, broilers, grills, roasters, kettles, etc</li>
 <li> Observing and testing foods being cooked by tasting, smelling, and piercing with thermometer to determine proper preparation and cooking</li>
 <li> Plating and portioning food and maintain consistency according to presentation specifications, using records or specs</li>
 <li> Labeling, dating and rotating all stored food</li>
 <li> Performing closing procedures including equipment maintenance and shut off, cleaning, sanitation, and organization of kitchen, walk-in coolers, and all storage areas</li>
</ul></br></br>
<b>Qualifications</b></br></br>This position may for you if: </br>
<ul>
 <li> You are 18 years old </li>
 <li> You have achieved a high school diploma or general education degree (GED) </li>
 <li> You have previous kitchen experience </li>
 <li> You are available to work days, evenings, weekends and holidays </li>
</ul>]]></jobdescription_opt>
      <jobid>13819_9541-6bcaed2becdae28c8ee08b64fdd4e008</jobid>
      <jobtitle>Line Cook | Beach House</jobtitle>
      <jobtype>FULL_TIME</jobtype>
      <location>Walloon Lake,MI,United States</location>
      <logo>https://dev-jbk-ai.s3.amazonaws.com/company-logos/d-uploads/1621582705622-Boyne_Resorts_Logo.png</logo>
      <occupationalcategory>35-2014.00,Cooks, Restaurant</occupationalcategory>
      <postalCode>49796</postalCode>
      <salary null="true" />
      <salaryEstimate null="true" />
      <sameas>https://boyneresorts.com/</sameas>
      <url>https://click.appcast.io/track/9gg4v66?cs=jsq&amp;exch=1a&amp;jg=3t1b&amp;bid=SSAKDDdbKVFCOLsOsUlBHA==</url>
   </job>
   <job>
      <company>Boyne Resorts</company>
      <jobdescription_opt><![CDATA[<b>Overview</b></br></br>As a 
<strong>Line Cook </strong>you are responsible for preparing food, helping the kitchen staff in preparation of food items, setting up assigned station in compliance with standards set by Chef. As a Boyne Mountain team member, there are so many awesome perks for you to take advantage of, such as: ski passes, golf passes, waterpark passes, and discounts for food, beverages, retail, daycare, and so much more! To learn more about Boyne Mountain Resort, employment perks, and employee testimonials, click here - Boyne Mountain Employment !</br></br>"Work Where You Love To Play!" at Boyne Mountain Resort.</br></br>
<b>Responsibilities</b></br></br>The 
<strong>Line Cook's </strong>typical job functions include: </br>
<ul>
 <li> Preparing food according to food handling guidelines and cooking procedures</li>
 <li> Measuring and mixing ingredients according to recipe or use record to prepare and prep food items</li>
 <li> Stocking and maintaining sufficient levels of food products at line stations to assure a smooth service period</li>
 <li> Communicating and coordinating production with other cooks, wait staff and members of the food and beverage team</li>
 <li> Possessing knowledge and/or become familiar with all kitchen equipment</li>
 <li> Adjusting thermostat controls to regulate temperature of ovens, broilers, grills, roasters, kettles, etc</li>
 <li> Observing and testing foods being cooked by tasting, smelling, and piercing with thermometer to determine proper preparation and cooking</li>
 <li> Plating and portioning food and maintain consistency according to presentation specifications, using records or specs</li>
 <li> Labeling, dating and rotating all stored food</li>
 <li> Performing closing procedures including equipment maintenance and shut off, cleaning, sanitation, and organization of kitchen, walk-in coolers, and all storage areas</li>
</ul></br></br>
<b>Qualifications</b></br></br>This position may for you if: </br>
<ul>
 <li> You are 18 years old </li>
 <li> You have achieved a high school diploma or general education degree (GED) </li>
 <li> You have previous kitchen experience </li>
 <li> You are available to work days, evenings, weekends and holidays </li>
</ul>]]></jobdescription_opt>
      <jobid>13819_9519-63db3ba2386ef041eaa95ed2b8836f80</jobid>
      <jobtitle>Line Cook | Everett's</jobtitle>
      <jobtype>FULL_TIME</jobtype>
      <location>Harbor Springs,MI,United States</location>
      <logo>https://dev-jbk-ai.s3.amazonaws.com/company-logos/d-uploads/1621582705622-Boyne_Resorts_Logo.png</logo>
      <occupationalcategory>35-2014.00,Cooks, Restaurant</occupationalcategory>
      <postalCode>49740</postalCode>
      <salary null="true" />
      <salaryEstimate null="true" />
      <sameas>https://boyneresorts.com/</sameas>
      <url>https://click.appcast.io/track/9gg4vaq?cs=jsq&amp;exch=1a&amp;jg=3t1b&amp;bid=SSAKDDdbKVFCOLsOsUlBHA==</url>
   </job>
   <job>
      <company>Boyne Resorts</company>
      <jobdescription_opt><![CDATA[<b>Overview</b></br></br>As a 
<strong>Line Cook </strong>you are responsible for preparing food, helping the kitchen staff in preparation of food items, setting up assigned station in compliance with standards set by Chef. As a Boyne Mountain team member, there are so many awesome perks for you to take advantage of, such as: ski passes, golf passes, waterpark passes, and discounts for food, beverages, retail, daycare, and so much more! To learn more about Boyne Mountain Resort, employment perks, and employee testimonials, click here - Boyne Mountain Employment !</br></br>"Work Where You Love To Play!" at Boyne Mountain Resort.</br></br>
<b>Responsibilities</b></br></br>The 
<strong>Line Cook's </strong>typical job functions include: </br>
<ul>
 <li> Preparing food according to food handling guidelines and cooking procedures</li>
 <li> Measuring and mixing ingredients according to recipe or use record to prepare and prep food items</li>
 <li> Stocking and maintaining sufficient levels of food products at line stations to assure a smooth service period</li>
 <li> Communicating and coordinating production with other cooks, wait staff and members of the food and beverage team</li>
 <li> Possessing knowledge and/or become familiar with all kitchen equipment</li>
 <li> Adjusting thermostat controls to regulate temperature of ovens, broilers, grills, roasters, kettles, etc</li>
 <li> Observing and testing foods being cooked by tasting, smelling, and piercing with thermometer to determine proper preparation and cooking</li>
 <li> Plating and portioning food and maintain consistency according to presentation specifications, using records or specs</li>
 <li> Labeling, dating and rotating all stored food</li>
 <li> Performing closing procedures including equipment maintenance and shut off, cleaning, sanitation, and organization of kitchen, walk-in coolers, and all storage areas</li>
</ul></br></br>
<b>Qualifications</b></br></br>This position may for you if: </br>
<ul>
 <li> You are 18 years old </li>
 <li> You have achieved a high school diploma or general education degree (GED) </li>
 <li> You have previous kitchen experience </li>
 <li> You are available to work days, evenings, weekends and holidays </li>
</ul>]]></jobdescription_opt>
      <jobid>13819_9519-aa569cae1e44fa56091a82ef9ecea0e9</jobid>
      <jobtitle>Line Cook | Everett's</jobtitle>
      <jobtype>FULL_TIME</jobtype>
      <location>Bay Shore,MI,United States</location>
      <logo>https://dev-jbk-ai.s3.amazonaws.com/company-logos/d-uploads/1621582705622-Boyne_Resorts_Logo.png</logo>
      <occupationalcategory>35-2014.00,Cooks, Restaurant</occupationalcategory>
      <postalCode>49711</postalCode>
      <salary null="true" />
      <salaryEstimate null="true" />
      <sameas>https://boyneresorts.com/</sameas>
      <url>https://click.appcast.io/track/9gg4v6l?cs=jsq&amp;exch=1a&amp;jg=3t1b&amp;bid=SSAKDDdbKVFCOLsOsUlBHA==</url>
   </job>
   <job>
      <company>Boyne Resorts</company>
      <jobdescription_opt><![CDATA[<b>Overview</b></br></br>As a 
<strong>Dishwasher </strong>you are responsible for keeping dish area, restaurant equipment and utensils in clean and orderly condition. As a Boyne Mountain team member, there are so many awesome perks for you to take advantage of, such as: ski passes, golf passes, waterpark passes, and discounts for food, beverages, retail, daycare, and so much more! To learn more about Boyne Mountain Resort, employment perks, and employee testimonials, click here - Boyne Mountain Employment !</br></br>"Work Where You Love To Play!" at Boyne Mountain Resort.</br></br>
<b>Responsibilities</b></br></br>The 
<strong>Dishwasher's </strong>typical job functions include: </br>
<ul>
 <li> Rinsing, scrubbing and scraping food from all dirty dishes, silverware, and cookware and washing them by hand or place them in racks or on conveyor to dishwashing machine</li>
 <li> Placing all clean dishes in proper storage areas</li>
 <li> Cleaning and maintaining work areas, equipment and utensils</li>
 <li> Removing garbage and place refuse in designated pickup area</li>
 <li> Cleaning drains, disposals and sinks to ensure proper drainage</li>
 <li> Following all health regulations and assisting in maintaining a sanitary environment</li>
 <li> Setting up dish machine and ensuring machine is operating properly</li>
 <li> Sweeping and moping kitchen floors</li>
 <li> Washing worktables, walls, refrigerators and other kitchen surfaces</li>
</ul></br></br>
<b>Qualifications</b></br></br>This position may be for you if: </br>
<ul>
 <li> You are at least 16 years old </li>
 <li> You are available to work days, evenings, weekends and holidays </li>
 <li> You are able to lift up to 25 pounds </li>
 <li> You are able to stand for long periods of time </li>
</ul>]]></jobdescription_opt>
      <jobid>13819_9544-feec894eda86602d2310ef53cc8e8f38</jobid>
      <jobtitle>Banquet Dishwasher</jobtitle>
      <jobtype>FULL_TIME</jobtype>
      <location>Brutus,MI,United States</location>
      <logo>https://dev-jbk-ai.s3.amazonaws.com/company-logos/d-uploads/1621582705622-Boyne_Resorts_Logo.png</logo>
      <occupationalcategory>35-9021.00,Dishwashers</occupationalcategory>
      <postalCode>49716</postalCode>
      <salary null="true" />
      <salaryEstimate null="true" />
      <sameas>https://boyneresorts.com/</sameas>
      <url>https://click.appcast.io/track/9gg4v8i?cs=jsq&amp;exch=1a&amp;jg=3t1b&amp;bid=SSAKDDdbKVFCOLsOsUlBHA==</url>
   </job>
   <job>
      <company>Boyne Resorts</company>
      <jobdescription_opt><![CDATA[<b>Overview</b></br></br>As a 
<strong>Dishwasher </strong>you are responsible for keeping dish area, restaurant equipment and utensils in clean and orderly condition. As a Boyne Mountain team member, there are so many awesome perks for you to take advantage of, such as: ski passes, golf passes, waterpark passes, and discounts for food, beverages, retail, daycare, and so much more! To learn more about Boyne Mountain Resort, employment perks, and employee testimonials, click here - Boyne Mountain Employment !</br></br>"Work Where You Love To Play!" at Boyne Mountain Resort.</br></br>
<b>Responsibilities</b></br></br>The 
<strong>Dishwasher's </strong>typical job functions include: </br>
<ul>
 <li> Rinsing, scrubbing and scraping food from all dirty dishes, silverware, and cookware and washing them by hand or place them in racks or on conveyor to dishwashing machine</li>
 <li> Placing all clean dishes in proper storage areas</li>
 <li> Cleaning and maintaining work areas, equipment and utensils</li>
 <li> Removing garbage and place refuse in designated pickup area</li>
 <li> Cleaning drains, disposals and sinks to ensure proper drainage</li>
 <li> Following all health regulations and assisting in maintaining a sanitary environment</li>
 <li> Setting up dish machine and ensuring machine is operating properly</li>
 <li> Sweeping and moping kitchen floors</li>
 <li> Washing worktables, walls, refrigerators and other kitchen surfaces</li>
</ul></br></br>
<b>Qualifications</b></br></br>This position may be for you if: </br>
<ul>
 <li> You are at least 16 years old </li>
 <li> You are available to work days, evenings, weekends and holidays </li>
 <li> You are able to lift up to 25 pounds </li>
 <li> You are able to stand for long periods of time </li>
</ul>]]></jobdescription_opt>
      <jobid>13819_9540-0e9197c0ab3fbc33ea24f63806887f31</jobid>
      <jobtitle>Dishwasher | Beach House</jobtitle>
      <jobtype>FULL_TIME</jobtype>
      <location>Vanderbilt,MI,United States</location>
      <logo>https://dev-jbk-ai.s3.amazonaws.com/company-logos/d-uploads/1621582705622-Boyne_Resorts_Logo.png</logo>
      <occupationalcategory />
      <postalCode>49795</postalCode>
      <salary null="true" />
      <salaryEstimate null="true" />
      <sameas>https://boyneresorts.com/</sameas>
      <url>https://click.appcast.io/track/9gg4v7k?cs=jsq&amp;exch=1a&amp;jg=3t1b&amp;bid=SSAKDDdbKVFCOLsOsUlBHA==</url>
   </job>
   <job>
      <company>Boyne Resorts</company>
      <jobdescription_opt><![CDATA[<b>Overview</b></br></br>As a 
<strong>Dishwasher </strong>you are responsible for keeping dish area, restaurant equipment and utensils in clean and orderly condition. As a Boyne Mountain team member, there are so many awesome perks for you to take advantage of, such as: ski passes, golf passes, waterpark passes, and discounts for food, beverages, retail, daycare, and so much more! To learn more about Boyne Mountain Resort, employment perks, and employee testimonials, click here - Boyne Mountain Employment !</br></br>"Work Where You Love To Play!" at Boyne Mountain Resort.</br></br>
<b>Responsibilities</b></br></br>The
<strong> Dishwasher's </strong>typical job functions include: </br>
<ul>
 <li> Rinsing, scrubbing and scraping food from all dirty dishes, silverware, and cookware and washing them by hand or place them in racks or on conveyor to dish washing machine</li>
 <li> Placing all clean dishes in proper storage areas</li>
 <li> Cleaning and maintaining work areas, equipment and utensils</li>
 <li> Removing garbage and place refuse in designated pickup area</li>
 <li> Cleaning drains, disposals and sinks to ensure proper drainage</li>
 <li> Following all health regulations and assisting in maintaining a sanitary environment</li>
 <li> Setting up dish machine and ensuring machine is operating properly</li>
 <li> Sweeping and moping kitchen floors</li>
 <li> Washing worktables, walls, refrigerators and other kitchen surfaces</li>
</ul></br></br>
<b>Qualifications</b></br></br>This position may be for you if: </br>
<ul>
 <li> You are at least 16 years old </li>
 <li> You are available to work days, evenings, weekends and holidays </li>
 <li> You are able to lift up to 25 pounds </li>
 <li> You are able to stand for long periods of time </li>
</ul>]]></jobdescription_opt>
      <jobid>13819_9518-5b21a5a6637959bdcd9f585d877d760e</jobid>
      <jobtitle>Dishwasher | Everett's</jobtitle>
      <jobtype>FULL_TIME</jobtype>
      <location>Wolverine,MI,United States</location>
      <logo>https://dev-jbk-ai.s3.amazonaws.com/company-logos/d-uploads/1621582705622-Boyne_Resorts_Logo.png</logo>
      <occupationalcategory>35-9021.00,Dishwashers</occupationalcategory>
      <postalCode>49799</postalCode>
      <salary null="true" />
      <salaryEstimate null="true" />
      <sameas>https://boyneresorts.com/</sameas>
      <url>https://click.appcast.io/track/9gg4v6i?cs=jsq&amp;exch=1a&amp;jg=3t1b&amp;bid=SSAKDDdbKVFCOLsOsUlBHA==</url>
   </job>
   <job>
      <company>Boyne Resorts</company>
      <jobdescription_opt><![CDATA[<b>Overview</b></br></br>On-site daycare at an affordable cost for active team members!</br></br>Looking for a new career opportunity? Consider Boyne Highlands Resort in Harbor Springs. Sure, we offer free golf and ski passes for our team members, but we're more than just a free pass.</br></br>Working at Boyne Highlands Resort gives you an opportunity to grow with us while we embark on a very exciting transformation! </br></br> Working at our resort is about being welcomed in as a member of the Highlands family. On average, our team members have been employed with us for over 7 years - and many have started in an entry level position and flourished with continued career advancement opportunities. </br></br> Ready to join the Highlands family? Check out the details below!</br></br>
<strong> Our Website </strong></br></br>
<strong> BOYNE HIGHLANDS RESORT </strong> is a family-owned, four-season destination located in Harbor Springs, Michigan and established in 1963. With 435 skiable acres, Boyne Highlands is the largest ski area in the Lower Peninsula and also offers the highest vertical terrain and mile-long runs. The winter season also offers Zipline Adventures, cross country skiing, snowshoeing, fat tire snow biking, the Aonach Mor Moonlight Dinner, and much more. The summer season delights with 72 holes of championship golf, a par-3 course, spa, horseback trail rides, biking, scenic chairlift rides, Segway PT Tours , and The Young Americans Dinner Theatre. </br>
<b>Team Member Benefits</b></br></br>Our team members get to experience all that our resort has to offer. Team members immediately receive great benefits like: </br>
<ul>
 <li> 40% discount on food and beverages in our restaurants </li>
 <li> 30% discount on spa services Sunday-Thursday </li>
 <li> FREE golf &amp; ski season passes </li>
 <li> Discounted adventure center activities </li>
 <li> Discounts on lodging for self and friends and family </li>
 <li> Friends and family vouchers </li>
 <li> Discounts on retail </li>
 <li> Child Care on site (affordable) </li>
 <li> 401k Eligible Immediately </li>
 <li> Team Member site: team.boynehighlands.com </li>
 <li> And so much more! </li>
</ul></br></br>
<b>Responsibilities</b></br></br>
<b>Qualifications</b></br></br>Boyne Highlands Resort is seeking applicants who are dedicated and excited to work hard and play hard.</br></br>
<strong>Qualities that will help you be successful:</strong> </br>
<ul>
 <li> Have a passion for guest service and the hospitality industry </li>
 <li> Display a friendly attitude and an outgoing personality </li>
 <li> Works well in team environment and projects a teamwork mentaility </li>
 <li> Helpful and kind when working with others. </li>
</ul></br> 
<strong>Highlighted Positions</strong> </br> 
<strong>Lodging:</strong> See all of our employment opportunities here --&gt; See options here </br> Housekeepers </br> Room Inspectors </br> Public Area Attendants </br> Front Desk </br></br> Security </br></br> 
<strong>Food and Beverage</strong> : </br></br> Line and Prep Cooks</br>Dishwashers </br> Hosts </br></br> Food Server/Bartender </br> Service Support]]></jobdescription_opt>
      <jobid>13819_9651-9ee77dc4c247d78389999f74aad880f3</jobid>
      <jobtitle>Ignite The Adventure at Boyne Highlands Resort - Landing Page</jobtitle>
      <jobtype>FULL_TIME</jobtype>
      <location>Oden,MI,United States</location>
      <logo>https://dev-jbk-ai.s3.amazonaws.com/company-logos/d-uploads/1621582705622-Boyne_Resorts_Logo.png</logo>
      <occupationalcategory />
      <postalCode>49764</postalCode>
      <salary null="true" />
      <salaryEstimate null="true" />
      <sameas>https://boyneresorts.com/</sameas>
      <url>https://click.appcast.io/track/97q2ziw?cs=jsq&amp;exch=1a&amp;jg=3t1a&amp;bid=SSAKDDdbKVFCOLsOsUlBHA==</url>
   </job>
   <job>
      <company>Boyne Resorts</company>
      <jobdescription_opt><![CDATA[<b>Overview</b></br></br>As a 
<strong>Dishwasher </strong>you are responsible for keeping dish area, restaurant equipment and utensils in clean and orderly condition. As a Boyne Mountain team member, there are so many awesome perks for you to take advantage of, such as: ski passes, golf passes, waterpark passes, and discounts for food, beverages, retail, daycare, and so much more! To learn more about Boyne Mountain Resort, employment perks, and employee testimonials, click here - Boyne Mountain Employment !</br></br>"Work Where You Love To Play!" at Boyne Mountain Resort.</br></br>
<b>Responsibilities</b></br></br>The 
<strong>Dishwasher's </strong>typical job functions include: </br>
<ul>
 <li> Rinsing, scrubbing and scraping food from all dirty dishes, silverware, and cookware and washing them by hand or place them in racks or on conveyor to dishwashing machine</li>
 <li> Placing all clean dishes in proper storage areas</li>
 <li> Cleaning and maintaining work areas, equipment and utensils</li>
 <li> Removing garbage and place refuse in designated pickup area</li>
 <li> Cleaning drains, disposals and sinks to ensure proper drainage</li>
 <li> Following all health regulations and assisting in maintaining a sanitary environment</li>
 <li> Setting up dish machine and ensuring machine is operating properly</li>
 <li> Sweeping and moping kitchen floors</li>
 <li> Washing worktables, walls, refrigerators and other kitchen surfaces</li>
</ul></br></br>
<b>Qualifications</b></br></br>This position may be for you if: </br>
<ul>
 <li> You are at least 16 years old </li>
 <li> You are available to work days, evenings, weekends and holidays </li>
 <li> You are able to lift up to 25 pounds </li>
 <li> You are able to stand for long periods of time </li>
</ul>]]></jobdescription_opt>
      <jobid>13819_9540-6bcaed2becdae28c8ee08b64fdd4e008</jobid>
      <jobtitle>Dishwasher | Beach House</jobtitle>
      <jobtype>FULL_TIME</jobtype>
      <location>Walloon Lake,MI,United States</location>
      <logo>https://dev-jbk-ai.s3.amazonaws.com/company-logos/d-uploads/1621582705622-Boyne_Resorts_Logo.png</logo>
      <occupationalcategory />
      <postalCode>49796</postalCode>
      <salary null="true" />
      <salaryEstimate null="true" />
      <sameas>https://boyneresorts.com/</sameas>
      <url>https://click.appcast.io/track/9gg4v9d?cs=jsq&amp;exch=1a&amp;jg=3t1b&amp;bid=SSAKDDdbKVFCOLsOsUlBHA==</url>
   </job>
   <job>
      <company>Boyne Resorts</company>
      <jobdescription_opt><![CDATA[<b>Overview</b></br></br>As a 
<strong>Dishwasher </strong>you are responsible for keeping dish area, restaurant equipment and utensils in clean and orderly condition. As a Boyne Mountain team member, there are so many awesome perks for you to take advantage of, such as: ski passes, golf passes, waterpark passes, and discounts for food, beverages, retail, daycare, and so much more! To learn more about Boyne Mountain Resort, employment perks, and employee testimonials, click here - Boyne Mountain Employment !</br></br>"Work Where You Love To Play!" at Boyne Mountain Resort.</br></br>
<b>Responsibilities</b></br></br>The 
<strong>Dishwasher's </strong>typical job functions include: </br>
<ul>
 <li> Rinsing, scrubbing and scraping food from all dirty dishes, silverware, and cookware and washing them by hand or place them in racks or on conveyor to dishwashing machine</li>
 <li> Placing all clean dishes in proper storage areas</li>
 <li> Cleaning and maintaining work areas, equipment and utensils</li>
 <li> Removing garbage and place refuse in designated pickup area</li>
 <li> Cleaning drains, disposals and sinks to ensure proper drainage</li>
 <li> Following all health regulations and assisting in maintaining a sanitary environment</li>
 <li> Setting up dish machine and ensuring machine is operating properly</li>
 <li> Sweeping and moping kitchen floors</li>
 <li> Washing worktables, walls, refrigerators and other kitchen surfaces</li>
</ul></br></br>
<b>Qualifications</b></br></br>This position may be for you if: </br>
<ul>
 <li> You are at least 16 years old </li>
 <li> You are available to work days, evenings, weekends and holidays </li>
 <li> You are able to lift up to 25 pounds </li>
 <li> You are able to stand for long periods of time </li>
</ul>]]></jobdescription_opt>
      <jobid>13819_9544-1afa411082397b5a2e499c33fbc4bd3b</jobid>
      <jobtitle>Banquet Dishwasher</jobtitle>
      <jobtype>FULL_TIME</jobtype>
      <location>Boyne City,MI,United States</location>
      <logo>https://dev-jbk-ai.s3.amazonaws.com/company-logos/d-uploads/1621582705622-Boyne_Resorts_Logo.png</logo>
      <occupationalcategory>35-9021.00,Dishwashers</occupationalcategory>
      <postalCode>49712</postalCode>
      <salary null="true" />
      <salaryEstimate null="true" />
      <sameas>https://boyneresorts.com/</sameas>
      <url>https://click.appcast.io/track/9gg4v4z?cs=jsq&amp;exch=1a&amp;jg=3t1b&amp;bid=SSAKDDdbKVFCOLsOsUlBHA==</url>
   </job>
   <job>
      <company>Boyne Resorts</company>
      <jobdescription_opt><![CDATA[<b>Overview</b></br></br>As a 
<strong>Dishwasher </strong>you are responsible for keeping dish area, restaurant equipment and utensils in clean and orderly condition. As a Boyne Mountain team member, there are so many awesome perks for you to take advantage of, such as: ski passes, golf passes, waterpark passes, and discounts for food, beverages, retail, daycare, and so much more! To learn more about Boyne Mountain Resort, employment perks, and employee testimonials, click here - Boyne Mountain Employment !</br></br>"Work Where You Love To Play!" at Boyne Mountain Resort.</br></br>
<b>Responsibilities</b></br></br>The 
<strong>Dishwasher's </strong>typical job functions include: </br>
<ul>
 <li> Rinsing, scrubbing and scraping food from all dirty dishes, silverware, and cookware and washing them by hand or place them in racks or on conveyor to dishwashing machine</li>
 <li> Placing all clean dishes in proper storage areas</li>
 <li> Cleaning and maintaining work areas, equipment and utensils</li>
 <li> Removing garbage and place refuse in designated pickup area</li>
 <li> Cleaning drains, disposals and sinks to ensure proper drainage</li>
 <li> Following all health regulations and assisting in maintaining a sanitary environment</li>
 <li> Setting up dish machine and ensuring machine is operating properly</li>
 <li> Sweeping and moping kitchen floors</li>
 <li> Washing worktables, walls, refrigerators and other kitchen surfaces</li>
</ul></br></br>
<b>Qualifications</b></br></br>This position may be for you if: </br>
<ul>
 <li> You are at least 16 years old </li>
 <li> You are available to work days, evenings, weekends and holidays </li>
 <li> You are able to lift up to 25 pounds </li>
 <li> You are able to stand for long periods of time </li>
</ul>]]></jobdescription_opt>
      <jobid>13819_9540-1afa411082397b5a2e499c33fbc4bd3b</jobid>
      <jobtitle>Dishwasher | Beach House</jobtitle>
      <jobtype>FULL_TIME</jobtype>
      <location>Boyne City,MI,United States</location>
      <logo>https://dev-jbk-ai.s3.amazonaws.com/company-logos/d-uploads/1621582705622-Boyne_Resorts_Logo.png</logo>
      <occupationalcategory />
      <postalCode>49712</postalCode>
      <salary null="true" />
      <salaryEstimate null="true" />
      <sameas>https://boyneresorts.com/</sameas>
      <url>https://click.appcast.io/track/9gg4v4s?cs=jsq&amp;exch=1a&amp;jg=3t1b&amp;bid=SSAKDDdbKVFCOLsOsUlBHA==</url>
   </job>
   <job>
      <company>Boyne Resorts</company>
      <jobdescription_opt><![CDATA[<b>Overview</b></br></br>As a 
<strong>Dishwasher </strong>you are responsible for keeping dish area, restaurant equipment and utensils in clean and orderly condition. As a Boyne Mountain team member, there are so many awesome perks for you to take advantage of, such as: ski passes, golf passes, waterpark passes, and discounts for food, beverages, retail, daycare, and so much more! To learn more about Boyne Mountain Resort, employment perks, and employee testimonials, click here - Boyne Mountain Employment !</br></br>"Work Where You Love To Play!" at Boyne Mountain Resort.</br></br>
<b>Responsibilities</b></br></br>The
<strong> Dishwasher's </strong>typical job functions include: </br>
<ul>
 <li> Rinsing, scrubbing and scraping food from all dirty dishes, silverware, and cookware and washing them by hand or place them in racks or on conveyor to dish washing machine</li>
 <li> Placing all clean dishes in proper storage areas</li>
 <li> Cleaning and maintaining work areas, equipment and utensils</li>
 <li> Removing garbage and place refuse in designated pickup area</li>
 <li> Cleaning drains, disposals and sinks to ensure proper drainage</li>
 <li> Following all health regulations and assisting in maintaining a sanitary environment</li>
 <li> Setting up dish machine and ensuring machine is operating properly</li>
 <li> Sweeping and moping kitchen floors</li>
 <li> Washing worktables, walls, refrigerators and other kitchen surfaces</li>
</ul></br></br>
<b>Qualifications</b></br></br>This position may be for you if: </br>
<ul>
 <li> You are at least 16 years old </li>
 <li> You are available to work days, evenings, weekends and holidays </li>
 <li> You are able to lift up to 25 pounds </li>
 <li> You are able to stand for long periods of time </li>
</ul>]]></jobdescription_opt>
      <jobid>13819_9518-0e9197c0ab3fbc33ea24f63806887f31</jobid>
      <jobtitle>Dishwasher | Everett's</jobtitle>
      <jobtype>FULL_TIME</jobtype>
      <location>Vanderbilt,MI,United States</location>
      <logo>https://dev-jbk-ai.s3.amazonaws.com/company-logos/d-uploads/1621582705622-Boyne_Resorts_Logo.png</logo>
      <occupationalcategory>35-9021.00,Dishwashers</occupationalcategory>
      <postalCode>49795</postalCode>
      <salary null="true" />
      <salaryEstimate null="true" />
      <sameas>https://boyneresorts.com/</sameas>
      <url>https://click.appcast.io/track/9gg4v54?cs=jsq&amp;exch=1a&amp;jg=3t1b&amp;bid=SSAKDDdbKVFCOLsOsUlBHA==</url>
   </job>
</jobs>
